[ 翻译：639 ]
[ 同步：Flake Chen ]
I felt like I had a lot of time.
我好像感觉我有很多时间。
I know.
我知道。
It's good.
I'm good.
那很好。
我很好。
Yeah. We're, um... we're
just getting off the freeway.
是啊。我们，呃…
我们刚下高速公路。
Yeah?
是吗？
Did, Hugh pick you up at the office, or...
休是去你办公室接的你还是……
Yeah, he was coming in from Oakland.
是的，他是从奥克兰过来的。
He was late, of course.
Then I took him...
当然他来晚了。
然后我带他…
And then, he took me to some lawyer bar.
然后他带我去了一个律师酒吧。
A lawyer bar?
律师酒吧？
Yeah. A lawyer bar, kind of.
是的，律师酒吧，像是吧。
Yeah. I don't know. Everybody
there seemed like a lawyer.
是啊，我不知道，
那里每个人都看着像律师。
I felt like I was the only
person without a tie.
我好像感觉只有我没系领带。
Well, maybe we should get you
a tie for emergencies.
是啊，也许应该给你
准备条急用的领带。
Yeah, wardrobe emergencies.
是啊，急用衣柜。
Yeah.
是啊。
Anyhow, we tried to take the freeway and...
一开始我们想走高速……
《相干》
Ke... Kevin?
凯…凯文？
《相干》
I can barely hear you.
我很难听清你。
Is that better?
这样好点吗？
Not much.
没好多少。
Where are you?
Are you there yet?
你在哪儿？
还在那儿吗？
Yeah, I... I'm just pulling up right now.
是的，我…我正想靠边停车呢。
I just got here.
Um...
我刚到这儿。
呃……
Yeah. I'm right here.
是的，我到这儿了。
I... You know what? I need to parallel
park and I'm not on my earpiece.
我…你看，我需要平行停车，
我得放下电话了。
Okay.
好的。
Are you good?
你还好吧？
Yeah.
好啊。
You know, we should talk about, you know...
你知道，我们应该谈谈，你知道……
Maybe we can talk about, you know,
也许我们可以谈谈，你知道，
that little problem before
we get into the party.
在参加聚会前
谈谈那个小问题。
Okay.
好啊。
Is it something we should
talk about now, or...
这事我们应该现在谈呢还是……
Hello?
喂？
Kevin?
凯文？
I lost you.
我听不见你。
Oh.
噢。
Baby?
宝贝？
You gotta be kidding me.
有痈愦恚
I think olive oil would be good.
A little more maybe?
我认为橄榄油就行。
也许再来点儿？
- A drizzle.
- A little more.
- 淋一些。
- 再加一点。
- Is this turning you on?
- That is hot.
- 是不是让你想入非非了？
- 很性感。
See how you're slipping?
This is...
你怎么那么浪费？
这……
- It's... It's the bread, babe.
- It's the two of you with the knives that...
- 这是…这是面包，宝贝。
- 你们两个拿刀的……
I have not had carbs for a week.
我已经一周没吃淀粉类食物了。
I've been on this... this "cleanse."
我现在正在…正在“辟谷”。
How long have you been cleansing for?
你已经辟谷多长时间了？
About 21 days.
大概21天了。
I had my juice and my
smoothie earlier today...
今天早些时候，
我吃了些果汁和沙冰，
and I do feel very, you know...
我的确感到很…你知道…
- Cleansed? Open?
- A little faint maybe?
- 被净化？很通畅？
- 还有点晕眩，也许？
But I'm gonna eat,
但我打算开吃了，
I'm gonna drink and have a good time.
我打算好吃好喝犒劳一下。
Hi.
嗨！
- Hey.
- How are you guys?
- 嘿！
- 你们好吗？
Nice to see you.
见到你太高兴了。
- Bend down to my level, please.
- I know.
- 弯下腰才能够着我吧。
- 是啊。
So, I just had Kevin on the
phone and this happened.
你们看，我刚才在和
凯文通话，可出了这事。
It cracked.
它爆裂了。
As I was talking to him.
我正在和他通话呢。
- You dropped it.
- Our connection... No, I didn't drop it.
- 你掉地上了？
- 我们的连线…不，我没掉地上。
It just cracked as I was holding it.
我拿在手里它就裂开了。
Do you have insurance?
你有保修吗？
I... I actually don't know if I do.
我…我说实话不知道。
Do you have the Skype app I showed you?
你有我推荐的讯佳普的应用吗？
No, I think it's fine. He just said
he wanted to talk about something,
不，我用得很好。
他说他想跟我谈什么事。
But on the news, you know,
they're talking about the comet.
但在新闻里，你们知道，
他们都在谈论那颗彗星。
- Yeah.
- The Miller's Comet.
- 是啊。
- 米勒彗星。
And they keep telling people
that this can happen.
他们一直在告诉大家
会发生这样的事情。
Yeah. I don't think it's the comet.
是的。但我不认为这是彗星引起的。
If you have Skype,
it uses the home Wi-Fi.
如果你有讯佳普，
它用家庭无线网络。
No. The interference.
They're saying things break.
不，因为干扰，
他们说东西会损坏。
Hey, do you want some wine?
嘿，你想来点酒吗？
Did Amir mention to you that...
阿米尔有没有向你提过…
he's bringing Laurie...
…他会带劳瑞…
to dinner?
…来吃饭？
He's bringing Laurie?
他会带劳瑞来？
Yeah. The Laurie.
是的，“那个”劳瑞。
Um, no, I didn't know that.
I didn't know that.
唔，没有，我不知道这事，
我不知道这事。
- Who's Laurie?
- Well, he is.
- 劳瑞是谁？
- 他会带来。
- You know Laurie.
- Oh, Mike.
- 你认识劳瑞的。
- 噢，迈克。
Long black hair. Kind of vixeny.
长黑发，狐媚又剽悍。
Wild and sexy.
野性又性感。
- Oh.
- Kinda strange, very mysterious.
- 噢……
- 些许奇怪、非常神秘。
- Very tight, tight, tight dresses.
- Listen.
- 穿非常紧身，很紧很紧的衣服。
- 听着，
It's totally fine.
It's such an Amir thing to do.
我完全没有问题。
这太像阿米尔的风格了。
I was going to keep this...
我一直带着这个…
This, my friends.
这个，我的朋友们。
It's my own little rescue remedy concoction.
这是我自己小小的拯救治疗制剂。
- Right.
- It's our own mix.
- 是吗？
- 是我们自己混合的。
- It's pretty s... It's very safe, I think.
- Do you want a needle for that?
- 它相当…它非常安全，我认为。
- 需要针筒注射吗？
- Is it clean?
- You can drop it into some water.
- 它纯净吗？
- 你可以滴在水里用。
Just take the edge off,
in case you're worried.
只是让你忘记烦恼，
不用担心别的。
I don't know.
I'm just... I'm offering.
我不知道，
我只是…我让你们自己选。
It's echinacea, passion
flower, a little valerian...
它是松果菊、西番莲、
一点缬草…
and ketamine.
…和开他敏（氯胺酮）。
- So it's all natural.
- Ketamine?
- 所以都是天然的。
- 开他敏？
That doesn't sound natural at all.
That's a horse tranquilizer.
那听上去一点也不天然，
那是给马用的镇静剂。
- Yeah, but it's just a whisper of ketamine.
- I did that once.
- 是的，但里面只有一丁点开他敏。
- 我曾用过一次。
I just thought maybe a celebration...
我只是想可能庆祝个……
Are you offering this to me,
because Laurie's coming here?
你是提供给我吗？
因为劳瑞要来？
Well, I'm just saying...
我只是随便说说……
- Now it's a party.
- Ketamine or cheese?
- 这样才像聚会嘛。
- 要开他敏还是奶酪？
It's right here if you change your mind.
Oh, this is nice.
就放这儿了，如果你改主意。
噢，这很漂亮。
Where'd you get this?
你从哪儿弄来的？
Galaxy, that thrift store.
“星系”，那家廉价商店。
- Oh, I love that place.
- Me too. I know.
- 噢，我喜欢那地方。
- 我也是，很不错。
Oh. Hi.
噢，嗨。
- Hi, baby.
- What?
- 嗨，宝贝。
- 什么？
- Come on. Come here.
- All right.
- 快点，过来这儿。
- 好吧。
My wife.
我老婆。
- Hi.
- Hey.
- 嗨。
- 嘿。
- How are you?
- Hi. I'm good.
- 你好吗？
- 嗨，我很好。
- Hi.
- 嗨。
- Do you guys want wine?
- I do.
- 你们俩想喝酒吗？
- 我想喝。
Cheese? Ketamine?
要奶酪？还是开他敏？
You look so good in leather.
你穿皮装太有型了。
Jesus Christ.
天哪。
- Um...
- I want water or something.
- 唔……
- 我想来点水或什么。
Did you know that, um,
你知道吗，唔…
- Laurie is coming?
- There you go.
- 劳瑞要来？
- 这下有戏看了。
No.
呃…不知道。
- Laurie's coming?
- Yeah.
- 劳瑞要来？
- 是的。
Look at the smile on your face.
看看你绽放的笑脸！
- It's not a smile. It's not that smile.
- Oh. my God.
- 不是笑脸，不是那种笑脸。
- 噢，我的天哪。
- Why is she coming tonight?
- Amir's bringing her.
- 为什么她今晚要来？
- 阿米尔要带她来。
Beats me, because Amir's a total jackass.
我不懂，阿米尔十足是个白痴。
Oh.
噢。
You know what? Put a quarter
into the swear jar.
你知道吗？罚你往
脏话罐里投两毛五分钱。
So, who did he tell?
那么他告诉谁了？
Well, we got the... Yeah.
唔，我们收到了…是啊…
We got an e-mail about it.
Just his plus one.
我们收的电子邮件里说的，
说他要“再加个人”。
Plus one and then I
was, like, plus what?
“再加个人”，然后我的
反应是“再加个她？”
I need to know tonight?
你今晚就需要知道？
My editor needs to know how
to book hotels and flights.
我的编辑需要了解
如何登记饭店和航班。
I gotta do it.
Let them know.
我不得不这样做。
告诉他们吧。
Gotta know tonight.
今晚就必须知道。
You know I-I... I can't...
你知道我…我…我不能……
I-I just need to think about it...
我…我需要考虑一下这事…
a little bit longer because...
再多点时间，因为…
I just don't want to make the wrong choice.
我真的不想做出错误的选择。
What if you came for a shorter time?
那你来的时间短一点如何？
Like a month, not the full four months.
Just come for a month.
比如说一个月，而不是
整四个月，就来一个月？
It's still a very long time...
那也很长了…
and I'm not saying no.
我并没有说“不行”。
Babe, if you don't say yes,
it becomes a no.
宝贝，如果你不说“行”，
那就成了“不行”。
We're cold and hungry.
我们又冷又饿。
Hello?
大家好啊？
- Hello.
- Hi.
- 你们好。
- 嗨。
- Amir, you look great.
- Thank you.
- 阿米尔，你看上去很棒。
- 谢谢。
- Hi.
- You remember Laurie?
- 嗨。
- 你还记得劳瑞吗？
Amir told me I wouldn't be...
阿米尔告诉我这样穿着不会…
- overdressed, now I'm feeling...
- No. No, no.
- …过分讲究，现在我觉得……
- 不，不，不，
We're underdressed.
是我们穿得太不讲究了。
- Hi.
- 嗨。
- How are you?
- I'm good.
- 你怎么样？
- 我很好。
- Beth, do you remember Laurie?
- Yes.
- 贝思，你记得劳瑞吧？
- 记得。
- Nice to see you.
- You guys already said hello and...
- 很高兴见到你。
- 你们已经打完招呼了……
How are you?
Good to see you.
你好吗？
很高兴见到你。
You guys want red wine?
你们想要红酒吗？
Yes. I would love red wine.
是的，我很想喝红酒。
- Lee?
- I've been cooking. I've been cooking.
- 李？
- 我正在做饭，我正在做饭。
- How have you been?
- I've been good. I've been really good.
- 你怎么样？
- 我很好，我真的很好。
- You?
- I've been great.
- 你呢？
- 我也很棒。
Yeah. Life is looking very different
from how it was a while back.
是啊，生活看起来
与以往大不相同。
- In a good way, so...
- Well, cool. That's good to hear.
- 当然是变好了，所以……
- 噢，不错，很高兴听你这么说。
- I would hope so. There you go.
- Thank you.
- 我希望如此。给你。
- 谢谢。
Not A, C, E.
不是A、C、E。
"Horace, listen.
“贺拉斯，你听着：
I'll be down at the pyramid.
Come on down and join.
“我会在金字塔下，
赶快下来加入我，
We gotta talk about some deity stuff."
“我们要谈谈关于神的一些东西。”
Does everyone else still not have service?
你们大家也还都没信号吗？
My phone is completely broken.
我的手机已经完全报废了。
I'm living in the moment, but...
我活在此刻，但……
- Nothing.
- I got zero.
- 什么都没有。
- 我的也没有。
That's weird.
Maybe the tower's down.
太奇怪了，
也许手机基站坏了。
The tower's down?
基站坏了？
I'm telling you guys...
我告诉你们……
- It's not down.
- That would be a big news story.
- 它没坏。
- 这会成为大新闻的。
Comet. Comet.
彗星。彗星。
- Miller's Comet.
- Yes. Thank you.
- 米勒彗星。
- 是的。谢谢。
I read something this morning
about a comet in the 1930s.
我今天上午读到篇有关
1930年代彗星的文章，
It was in Finland.
那是在芬兰。
- Knocked out all of the...
- I actually...
- 摧毁了所有的…
- 实际上我……
the cell towers?
…手机基站？
Actually, it was in 1923.
实际上那是在1923年。
And, yes, it was in Finland.
是的，是在芬兰。
- Um...
- Thank you, Wikipedia.
- 唔…
- 谢谢，维基百科。
It was actually crazy,
because it affected the people.
实际上那事很荒唐，
因为它影响到了人。
After it passed, they would get lost.
彗星过去后，人们都迷失了。
They would end up in the wrong home.
They would forget things.
最后他们有没呆在自己家里的，
有忘记事情的，
They wouldn't really know where they were.
有不知道自己身处何方的。
And I remember reading
about this one woman...
我记得读到有这样一个女人，
who called the police and said,
她报警说：
"The man in my house is not my husband."
“在我房子里的男人不是我丈夫。”
And then police came over...
然后警察过来了，
and they said, "This is your husband,"
他们说：“这就是你丈夫。”
And she said, "No. This is not my husband.
她说：“不，这不是我丈夫。”
- I killed my husband yesterday.
- Awesome.
- “我昨天杀了我丈夫，
- 好赞。
That's how I know it's not him."
“所以我知道这不是他。”
But they couldn't arrest her,
because he was standing...
但他们不能逮捕她，
因为他就站在那里，
right there in front in them.
就站在他们面前。
Do they have any theories of why?
有什么解释吗为什么会这样？
Think how lucky she is.
She gets to kill him again.
想想她多幸运啊，
可以再杀他一次。
Clearly she wants to kill this man.
显然她想杀死这个男人。
- It's just the Finnish.
- The Finns.
- 芬兰人干得出来。
- 这些芬兰人啊。
The Finns or Finnish?
芬兰人怎么拼？
- You guys remember Halley's Comet?
- Yes.
- 你们还记得哈雷彗星吗？
- 记得。
I mean, it was such a big deal.
我是说，那在当时可是大事。
【应该是指1986年的回归】
I remember at my school, we all had
to, like, reenact Halley's Comet.
我记得在我们学校，我们都要
参与模拟哈雷彗星的回归。
So, they assigned each of us
something celestial to do.
所以他们分派给我们
每个人扮演某个天体。
My sister got to be Halley's Comet.
I was very jealous.
我姐姐正好扮演哈雷彗星，
我当时非常嫉妒。
I've never met your sister.
Have you guys met her sister?
我从没见过你姐姐。
你们有谁见过她姐姐吗？
There's a picture of her right
over there on the mantel, but...
那儿有张她的照片，
就在壁炉架上面，但…
- She's only a fleeting comet.
- she looks a little ridiculous.
- 她只是个飞逝而过的彗星。
- …她看上去有点可笑。
- That's your sister?
- But why did you put it...
- 那是你姐姐？
- 可你为什么把它放在……
It's the door to nowhere.
那道门不通向任何地方。
In feng shui, a useless door,
根据风水，一道无用之门，
which this is obviously a useless door,
这显然是一道无用之门，
you put a picture of someone...
你放上某个与你有…
you have unresolved issues with...
…未解纠纷的人的照片……
and it causes all
of this weird energy flow.
那会导致各种诡异的能量流动。
I don't even like being over here.
我都不想靠近这儿。
- It's freaky.
- You shouldn't be over there then.
- 很可怕，真的……
- 那你不该在那儿。
- Every time you're...
- I'm sort of an empath.
- 每次你这样说……
- 我好像具有神入的本领。
- Sort of an empath.
- And I can feel it. It's like a vortex.
- 某种神入。
- 我可以感觉到，那像是一个涡流。
When was the last time we
were all together like this?
我们上次像这样
聚在一起是什么时候？
I was thinking,
right before Thanksgiving,
我也在想呢，
就在感恩节之前，
most of us were there,
but not everybody could be.
我们中大部分都在那儿，
不过不可能是全部。
I don't think Laurie...
Laura?
我觉得劳瑞就没…
还是劳拉？
- Laurie.
- 劳瑞。
Sorry. We're gonna tell
all these stories.
对不起。我们要说说
自己的故事，
We do that when we get together.
我们聚会时都这么做。
So Laurie, what are you doing these days?
那么劳瑞，目前你从事哪行呢？
- Well, I'm...
- Keeping yourself busy?
- 噢，我…
- 你在忙些啥？
I'm keeping busy.
我一直很忙。
I'm actually working with some
outreach programs in Silicon Valley.
其实我在做硅谷的
一些外展项目，
We work with at-risk youth.
我们从事危机青少年工作。
Oh, wow. Didn't you...
No, no, no.
噢，哇哦。你没有…
不，不，不。
Are you still teaching the yoga?
你还在教瑜伽吗？
The Spanish Yoga? The Spoga?
教西班牙瑜伽？“西班伽”？
- No. Not me.
- Are you sure that...
- 不，不是我。
- 你确定那……
Oh, that must've been another girl...
噢，那一定是另一个女孩…
that Kevin dated that
Amir is hooking up with.
…凯文曾约会过，
现在又和阿米尔好上了。
Wow. Let's give him a shovel.
哇哦，我们给他把铁锹。
What are you doing?
What do you do for a living?
你做什么呢？
你靠什么谋生？
I act.
Shut up, guys.
我表演。
闭嘴，都给我。
I didn't remember you were an actor.
我不记得你是演员。
- So, you do mainly theater?
- Well, I did.
- 那么你主要在剧场演？
- 唔，我演过。
Since I moved down here to support
my wife and her Skyping career.
自从我搬来这里支持
我老婆和她的讯佳普事业。
Um, but, no, I was in a TV
show for about four years.
唔，但我以前出演过
一个电视剧，有大约四年。
- Yeah? What was that?
- It was called Roswell.
- 是吗？是哪部剧？
- 名叫《罗斯韦尔》。
Oh, my God.
I love Roswell.
噢，我的天哪！
我爱《罗斯韦尔》！
When were you on Roswell?
What episodes were you on?
《罗斯韦尔》那一段里有你？
你出现在哪一集？
I was on all shows.
Produced.
所有集里都有我，
已出的那些。
- What do you mean?
- I was a series regular on that show.
- 你什么意思？
- 我是那部系列剧的常规演员。
Yeah, he was, like, the main guy.
是啊，他可以说是主要人物。
What character did you play?
你演的是哪个角色？
- Joe.
- Did you have different hair, or something?
- 乔。
- 你的头发有变过吗？还是……
I had the same exact hair.
我一直是这样的头发。
I'm sorry. Maybe it's one of
those things where you know...
不好意思，这可能有点像那种
你明明认识某个角色…
the character for so long, then you see
someone in person. It just doesn't compute.
…很长时间了，但当你见到
他本人时，却怎么也对不上。
I don't know.
我不知道。
- He's sort of grown into his face.
- You really have.
- 他现在脸上有点长胖了。
- 真的是的。
Check it out again.
你再想想看呢。
I'm sure, you know, like the downward
dog probably gets to your head.
我相信，你知道，你做
狗趴弯腰什么的让你脑子糊涂了。
- I didn't do yoga. That wasn't...
- Well, hey, listen.
- 我不做瑜伽。那不是……
- 好吧，嘿，听着，
Thanks for enjoying the show.
谢谢观赏我的表演。
I think you are a really good actor...
我觉得你真的是个好演员，
and I think you should continue doing it.
而且我觉得你应该继续演下去。
- Thank you very much.
- I think it would be well worth your time.
- 非常感谢。
- 我觉得你值得花时间去做。
What are you up to these days?
你目前做什么呢？
Last I remember, you were, like,
上次我记得你好像…
taking the dance world by storm.
…向舞蹈界发起了猛攻。
Um, I guess the last time I saw you...
唔，我想上次我见你…
must've been when I was
creating the dance show.
…一定是我在创作
那部舞剧的时候。
It was going really,
really well for a while,
那部戏一开始都进展得
相当相当顺利，
but then, right before the,
um... the premiere,
但是后来，就在呃…首演之前，
they brought in Svetlana Aserrano...
他们找来了斯维特兰娜・阿塞拉诺…
who is the best dancer in the world really,
她当然是现今世上最好的舞蹈家，
and they just offered me the understudy.
所以他们让我做了替补。
She should've been the whole thing.
这部剧整个都是她的，
She created it.
She should be the prima ballerina...
是她创作的。
她才应该是旧金山芭蕾舞团的…
- of the San Francisco Ballet.
- That's terrible.
- …首席女演员。
- 太可怕了。
You know, you hear these stories sometimes...
你知道，有时你会听说这样的故事，
about people being shut out
of things they created...
有人创造出了什么东西
却被排挤在外……
and I think it's horrible.
I'm sorry.
我觉得这太可怕了。
我很抱歉。
But I mean it's a good lesson
that I had to learn, because...
不过我好像从这件事中
学到了不少教训，因为…
You know, because of my pride,
I didn't want...
你知道，因为我的骄傲，
我不太愿意…
to take the understudy
and I took too long...
…接受替补的角色，
所以我考虑了…
to think about it and then
I lost the understudy job.
…太长的时间以至于
我丢掉了替补席的工作。
And they gave that to
Katherine Meriss and...
他们把替补给了
凯瑟琳・梅里斯，所以……
And she sucks.
她好烂呐。
- She sucks.
- No, she's good, guys.
- 她烂透了。
- 不，她还好吧，各位。
Anyways, the reason
that she's really big now...
总之，为什么现在
她成了真正的大腕…
is because she ended up going up.
…是因为她最后顶了上去。
Svetlana pulled out last minute...
斯维特兰娜在最后一刻退出了…
and Katherine ended up doing the show.
而凯瑟琳最终成了主演。
- Katherine Meriss?
- Exactly.
- 凯瑟琳・梅里斯？
- 没错。
As soon as you said that, I
thought, "Katherine Meriss...
你说这些的时候，我的第一
反应是：“凯瑟琳・梅里斯…
that's pretty much the only
person in dance I'd know."
“…大概是舞蹈界
我知道的唯一的人。”
Right. Well...
是啊。可是……
So, she basically stole
your... your whole thing?
所以她可以说是
偷走了你的…你的一切？
Katherine Meriss has
your life, basically.
凯瑟琳・梅里斯占有了
你的生活，可以这么说。
- Career.
- You have your life.
- 是事业。
- 你有你的生活。
It's a shame that it happened.
She doesn't hold a candle to you.
很可惜发生这样的事，
她连给你提鞋都不配。
Then, here's to the life that we do lead.
好吧，为我们现在过的生活干杯。
- Yeah.
- Well said.
- 是啊。
- 说得好。
- Here's to the comet.
- The comet. And the comet.
- 下面为彗星干杯。
- 敬彗星。敬彗星。
Anybody have a happier story?
谁来讲个高兴点的故事？
Kevin, tell a crazy story,
first one that comes in your head.
凯文，你讲个疯狂的故事，
第一个在你头脑里冒出来的。
No. All right.
不。好吧。
Um... Sorry.
唔…对不起了。
I was going out with Laurie.
我有次和劳瑞一起出去，
We were drinking way too much at a bar.
我们在酒吧喝了太多的酒。
I passed out and I started dreaming...
我失去了知觉，开始做梦…
this big black bear...
梦见一头很大的黑熊…
was up on its hind legs sort of mauling me.
…正支着它的后腿好像在挠我。
Slowly. Tenderly.
慢慢地、轻轻地。
Anyhow, we go to some party...
后来，我们去参加某个聚会，
in Santa Cruz and as we walked in,
在圣塔克鲁兹，当我们走进去时，
this huge dog comes running straight at me.
有条巨大的狗直直地冲向我，
Jumps up on its hind legs
and starts pawing me,
跳起来用后腿支撑着，
并开始抓我，
exactly like the dream,
and this guy yells,
和梦中一模一样，
然后有个家伙喊道：
- "Bear, get down, Bear."
- What?
- “熊，下来，熊！”
- 什么？
Wow. You have a gift.
哇哦！太绘声绘色了。
The way you told that story, I thought...
你讲这故事的方式，让我想到…
somebody was going to die.
…一定有人要死了。
You know Bear is the most common dog name.
你知道狗最常用的取名就是“熊”。
Oh, that makes it a much
less interesting story.
噢，你这样一说
这故事一下无趣了很多。
Thanks for that, Lee.
谢谢你扫兴，李。
Most common bear name? Henry.
熊最常用的名字？亨利。
- Look.
- Oh, my God.
- 你看。
- 噢，我的天哪！
- What?
- This is like your phone.
- 什么？
- 这和你手机一样了。
Oh, my God. That happened
to my phone tonight.
噢，我的天哪。我的手机
今晚就变成了这样。
And I was just holding mine in my hand.
我当时正握着我的手机。
- Exact same thing.
- Shattered?
- 完全一样。
- 碎掉了？
Yeah. This is what they were
talking about on the news.
是啊。这就是他们
在新闻里谈论的事。
Yeah. Yeah.
It must be the comet.
是的，是的。
一定是因为彗星。
- The chicken tastes like tuna.
- All right.
- 鸡肉的味道像金枪鱼，
- 行了。
It must be Miller's Comet.
一定也是因为米勒彗星。
So, nobody's phone works?
所以没人的手机能打？
I haven't checked mine,
but I assume it doesn't.
我还没看过我的，
但我猜一样不能打。
Everyone else's is in the other room.
其他人手机在另一个房间。
- Do you guys have a landline?
- No. We're wireless, baby.
- 你们家有座机吗？
- 没有，我们都用无线，宝贝。
All right. I need to get ahold of my brother.
好吧。我需要联系上我弟弟。
- What about, um, your deal...
- The computer.
- 那你的，呃…你做交易的……
- 电脑。
- Good idea.
- It's in the office.
- 好主意。
- 它在办公室。
- Could I?
- Yeah, yeah. Thanks.
- 我能用吗？
- 好，好。谢谢。
- What's wrong with your brother?
- Nothing. He's fine.
- 你弟弟怎么了？
- 没什么，他很好。
He just, um...
You know Brian.
只是，唔……
你认识布赖恩的。
He hangs out with all those, you
know, theoretical physicists.
他总是和那些，你知道，
理论物理学家呆在一起。
- No Internet.
- No?
- 上不了因特网。
- 不行吗？
- On the computer.
- How is there no Internet?
- 电脑上不了。
- 怎么会上不了因特网。
- You run Skype. You tell us.
- I know.
- 你用讯佳普，你告诉我们原因。
- 我知道。
What are they saying about the comet?
那帮物理学家怎么说彗星的？
Nothing... Nothing to get upset about.
没什么…没什么好担心的。
He just said to give him a call,
他只是让我给他打个电话，
you know, if there was
anything weird going on.
你知道，如果发生什么
怪异的事情的话。
Like, why? What did he think it could do?
为什么啊？他觉得彗星会怎么样？
Why didn't you tell me this?
你怎么没告诉过我这事？
Because of your feng shui...
因为你的风水…
- and granola candles, and I didn't want to...
- Stop making fun of me.
- …和香味蜡烛，我不想……
- 别寻我开心。
I'm not making fun of you.
我没寻你开心。
There's a massive celestial object,
有个巨大的天体要出现了，
and I didn't want to freak you out.
我不想让你吓到。
- Now you're freaking me out.
- You guys realize...
- 现在你吓到我了。
- 各位别忘了…
I was on a show called Roswell...
…我演过的剧叫《罗斯韦尔》，
and we tackled these issues every week.
我们每星期都在应付这些问题。
That's true.
那倒是的。
- Oh, shit.
- Oh, my God.
- 噢，见鬼。
- 噢，我的天哪。
- Honey.
- Um, I'm on it.
- 亲爱的。
- 唔，我来想办法。
Do we have candles?
我们有蜡烛吗？
I'm so glad I'm not high.
我太高兴了我还清醒。
I don't want to sit by the door to nowhere.
我不想坐在这道无用之门旁边。
Mike, check the breakers.
迈克，检查一下电门保险。
I'm going to turn the lighter on
then come to you.
我要去开荧光棒，
然后来找你们。
- You guys need help?
- No. I have matches.
- 你们有谁需要帮忙？
- 不用，我有火柴。
- Candle power?
- I've got some over here.
- 烛光？
- 我已经在这里找到一些。
I got blue glowsticks, red
glowsticks and green glowsticks.
我这儿有蓝荧光棒、
红荧光棒、和绿荧光棒。
Guys, let's just light candles and...
各位，我们还是点蜡烛吧……
Oh.
噢。
- Hey.
- Everybody rave.
- 嘿。
- 大家一起狂欢。
- Are you going outside?
- Yeah.
- 你们要到外面去吗？
- 是的。
What do you mean, you're going outside?
什么意思，你们要出去？
I'm gonna see if the power's
off in the whole neighborhood.
我想去看一下整个这附近
是否也停电了。
I decided this is where mine goes.
我决定我的就放这儿了。
Well, this is a little strange,
唔，这事有点奇怪，
but the whole neighborhood is out...
整个这附近都停电了，
of power, except for a house
about two blocks up,
除了两街区外的一所房子，
which is completely lit up.
那里灯火通明。
It's kind of beautiful, actually.
还蛮漂亮的，说实话。
- The house?
- I want to go see.
- 房子？
- 我也想去看看。
- Let's go check it out.
- I've never seen it so dark outside before.
- 我们都去看看吧。
- 以前从没见过外面这么黑的。
- You can't leave me. I'm gonna go.
- Come on then.
- 你们不能撇下我，我也要去。
- 那就走吧。
Don't leave me by myself.
别把我一个人留下。
- Where?
- You don't see it?
- 在哪儿？
- 你没看见吗？
- It's right there.
- Why are you so far ahead of everyone?
- 就在那儿。
- 你为什么一个人跑那么快？
Amir, dude, I can't see you.
阿米尔，老兄，我看不见你。
- Let Laurie go first.
- Thanks a lot.
- 让劳瑞先走。
- 多谢。
- That's sweet.
- Baby. Don't go.
- 你太好了。
- 宝贝，别去啊。
- Come here.
- See? Look.
- 到这边来。
- 看到了？你看。
- Everything done.
- Come here.
- 一片漆黑。
- 过来。
See that?
看到那没有？
- Two blocks down.
- Oh, they have light.
- 两个街区之外。
- 噢，他们有光。
- That one house has light.
- They must have a...
- 只有一家有光。
- 他们一定有……
- A generator, or something?
- Yeah, yeah.
- 发电机之类的？
- 是的，是的。
What is that, two blocks away?
那有多远，隔两个街区？
Could solar power do that?
可能是用太阳能吗？
But would their landline be working?
他们的座机会能用吗？
Oh, wow. Look at that.
噢，哇哦！你看那儿！
- Oh, wow.
- It's magnificent.
- 噢，哇哦！
- 太壮观了！
Holy moly.
老天爷啊！
Well, I'm freezing.
我冻死了。
Should we head over there, or should we...
我们是过去看看呢还是……
- No.
- Maybe we should head back inside.
- 不。
- 也许我该回屋里去了。
That was awesome, right?
那太棒了，对吗？
- I didn't even see this get knocked over.
- No.
- 我怎么没注意这杯子碎了。
- 是啊。
I didn't even know that glass was out here.
我都不记得这玻璃杯刚才在这儿。
I never go down into the basement.
我决不去地下室。
Guys, listen. Seriously,
what's up with that house?
各位，听着：说真的，
那所房子是怎么回事？
- Why are they...?
- What?
- 为什么他们……？
- 什么？
It could be a generator.
可能他们用了发电机。
Really?
真的吗？
I don't know. Maybe they're
just off-the-grid bastard...
我不知道，也许那帮混蛋
压根没用这个电网……
Well, apparently, we have a generator.
显然，我们也有发电机。
That would make sense if
they were off the grid.
如果他们没用我们的电网，
那就说得通了。
I'm actually thinking of...
of going over there.
我其实在想…
想要过去看看。
What?
什么？
- No, you're not going over there.
- Honey, it's okay.
- 不，你不能过去。
- 亲爱的，没事的。
- It's o...
- It's ridiculous.
- 没什么……
- 太荒唐了。
It's not that far.
Look, look, look, look.
那儿没多远。
你看，你看。
My brother, he says...
我弟弟，他说…
he said that if... if anything
strange were to happen...
他说如果…如果
在彗星经过时…
while the comet was passing over...
发生了什么奇怪的事，
- that we should stay inside.
- What?
- 我们应该呆在房间里。
- 什么？
Just hold on, Amir.
等一下，阿米尔。
That we should stay inside and that
I should do my best to contact him.
他说我们应该呆在房间里，
而我应该尽力和他联系。
And so that's all that I'm doing.
这就是我正在做的。
He said if anything strange
should happen? I mean...
他说过会发生奇怪的事吗？
我是说……
I'm not the only one who
thinks this is strange.
不止我一个人觉得这事很奇怪。
- What is weird?
- Didn't he say to stay inside though?
- 什么很奇怪？
- 他说过要呆在房间里吗？
What's more important than the other?
所以重要的是要呆在房间里？
Yes, but this overrides that,
and it's only two blocks away.
是的，但这比那还重要，
再说那儿只隔了两个街区。
I'll be back in, like, five minutes.
我会在，多少，五分钟内返回。
- Well, then you can't go by yourself.
- I'm going with him.
- 好吧，要去你自己去吧。
- 我和他一起去。
There you go. I'll take Amir.
好的，我带上阿米尔。
- I'm the least important person here.
- This is true.
- 我是这里最微不足道的人。
- 那倒是的。
It's about time you started realizing that.
是到了你开始意识到这点的时候了。
- Just stay here.
- Why are you going now?
- 就呆在这儿。
- 你为什么现在去？
Well, bring your glowsticks
so we can identify your bodies.
好吧，拿上你们的荧光棒，
好让我们辨别你们的身份。
- Good idea.
- Thanks. That helps a lot.
- 好主意。
- 谢谢，那帮了大忙。
- Don't listen to them.
- That's great.
- 别听他们的。
- 太好了。
Five minutes, all right?
就五分钟，行吗？
- Okay. Five minutes.
- All right. Okay.
- 好吧，五分钟。
- 好的，没问题。
Beth, I-I couldn't find my shoes.
贝思，我…我找不到我的鞋了。
I'm borrowing yours. I'm sorry.
我借你的穿，对不起。
That's so Amir.
真是太阿米尔了。
- Ten minutes we give them.
- They will be fine.
- 十分钟我们给他们。
- 他们没事的。
We're just rattled because we're
addicted to cell phones and Internet.
我们这么慌乱是因为我们
太离不开手机和因特网了。
We are. What did we do before cell phones?
是的，在有手机前我们做什么？
Em, you seem to be the
comet expert here tonight.
艾米，你好像是
今晚这里的彗星专家，
What happened the last time?
上一次发生过什么？
This one passed over a hundred
years ago, but much farther.
这颗彗星一百年前
经过过，只是远得多。
But do we know that anything happened?
但我们知道发生过什么事吗？
Nothing happened then.
It was too far away.
当时什么事都没发生，
它距离太远了。
So, is there any reason...
那这一次有没有理由…
we should be freaked out right now?
…我们应该感到担心呢？
Well, I mean, it is
a lot closer this time.
唔，我想说，
这一次它近了好多。
What does that mean?
那意味着什么呢？
Okay. I read one more thing.
好吧，我还读过一篇文章。
- Oh, another story.
- Just one more.
- 噢，又要讲故事。
- 再讲一个。
It's called the Tunguska Event...
它叫“通古斯事件”，
and, um, it was a comet...
唔，那是颗彗星…
or a meteor or something like that...
…或是一颗流星或诸如此类的…
that entered the atmosphere over Siberia...
进入了西伯利亚上空的大气层，
and exploded over Earth.
然后在地面之上爆炸。
So, it didn't actually have physical impact.
所以，其实它没有物理上的碰撞，
It didn't touch Earth.
它没有触到地球，
It didn't leave a crater or anything,
没有留下环形山之类的东西，
but the force of that explosion...
但是那个爆炸的力量…
flattened trees for hundreds of miles.
…削平了数百英里的树木，
But it only killed about one to two people.
但只杀死了一两个人。
It's Siberia. There were
probably only two people there.
那是西伯利亚，
可能那里也就只有两个人。
Yeah, but they don't necessarily...
是啊，但他们不一定……
- It wiped out the population of Siberia.
- Basically. Yeah.
- 它清除了西伯利亚的人口。
- 大致上，是的。
- Right.
- Well, that doesn't make me feel better.
- 是的。
- 可这没让我感觉好点。
And when was this?
这什么时候的事？
It was, like, in 1908, 1903...
好像是1908还是1903……
Oh, my God, oh, my God,
oh, my God. What is...
噢，我的天哪！噢，我的天哪！
噢，我的天哪！那是……？
- What the fuck was that?
- I don't know.
- 那他妈的是什么？
- 我不知道。
- Lock that front door.
- Don't open the door.
- 把前门锁上。
- 别打开门。
- I'm gonna get the bat.
- Yeah. Give me the bat.
- 我去取棒球棒。
- 好的，拿球棒给我。
Mike, is that door locked?
迈克，那门锁上了吗
- I'll check it.
- Babe, stay away from the door.
- 我去看看。
- 宝贝，别靠近那门。
- You need the stick?
- Thank you.
- 你需要球棒？
- 谢谢。
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
- I just want to see what the hell is out there.
- Oh, my God.
- 我想看看外面到底有什么。
- 噢，我的天哪。
- Don't open it.
- Oh, God.
- 别开门。
- 噢，天哪。
Please, don't open that.
求你了，别开那门。
- Is anybody there?
- Front door's locked. There's nothing.
- 有人在那儿吗？
- 前门锁上了，什么都没有。
There's nothing out there.
那儿什么都没有。
Thought I was going to have a heart attack.
我都要吓出心脏病来了。
Everybody all right?
大家都好吗？
Check the generator, please.
Please try the generator.
去看看发电机，求你了。
请去试一下发电机。
- I'll check the generator.
- Would the guys do that?
- 我去检查发电机。
- 会是那两个家伙干的吗？
No. The guys would not do anything like that.
不，那两个家伙不会干这样的事。
They're not stupid.
They wouldn't do that.
他们又不是傻瓜，
不会干出这样的事。
- How long have they been gone?
- Like ten minutes.
- 他们走了多长时间了？
- 有十分钟了吧。
Five minutes out, five minutes back.
They should be back by now.
五分钟过去，五分钟回来，
他们应该现在就回来了。
So, they should be back by now.
所以他们应该现在就回来了。
- Okay. I think we should go get them.
- No, no, no.
- 好吧。我认为我们应该去找他们。
- 不，不，不。
I want to go get my husband.
我想去找我老公。
We need to do it together this time, guys.
这一次我们需要一起行动，各位。
That's fine with me.
I just want to go.
我没问题，我只想去找。
- Don't go outside.
- I'm not going anywhere. I'm just...
- 别到外面去。
- 我哪儿也不想去，我只想……
We should go get them.
We can all go together.
我们应该去找他们，
我们可以一起过去。
Okay, all right. This is good.
好了，很好。这下好了。
Is that the grid or the generator?
是电网还是发电机给的电？
No, it's just us.
He must have gotten it going.
不，只有我们有电。
一定是他弄好的。
There's no other lights on?
It's just us?
别的地方都没灯光？
只有我们有？
- It's pitch black out there. At least it's on.
- So it must be...
- 外面一片漆黑。好在我们有了。
- 所以那一定是……
- Well done.
- Thank you.
- 干得好。
- 谢谢。
- You did it.
- Let there be light.
- 你弄好了。
- “要有光”。
Okay. Well, I think that we should...
好了。我觉得我们应该……
As a group, we should go find those guys.
作为团体，我们应该去找那两个家伙。
- I agree.
- Let's do it as a group this time.
- 我同意。
- 这次我们一起去找。
No. That's ridiculous.
不，那太荒唐了。
If you get lost in the woods,
you're supposed...
如果你在林中迷路了，
你应该…
to stay where you are until
someone can find you.
…留在原地直到有人发现你。
Fine. That's great. Let's
just sit down and breathe.
好吧，很好。
那我们就坐下来深呼吸吧。
For once, I actually agree
with what you're saying.
好吧，这一次我其实同意你说的。
You know what? You've been
giving me shit all night.
你知道吗？整个晚上
你一直在找我的茬。
- I am agreeing with you.
- Guys, guys, guys.
- 我同意你说的了。
- 各位，各位，各位。
I don't like any of this.
我一点也不喜欢这样。
Jesus!
天哪！
Stay.
别动。
Oh, my God.
噢，我的天哪。
Oh man, it's them.
噢，天哪，是他们。
- What the hell happened?
- Are you okay?
- 到底出什么事了？
- 你还好吗？
- I'm fine, I'm fine.
- Are you okay?
- 我没事，我很好。
- 你还好吧？
What is this?
这是什么？
- What's the box?
- That was at the other house.
- 这盒子是什么？
- 那是另一所房子里的。
I thought I saw Hugh put it down.
我以为我看见是休把它放下，
Then he was running around the corner and...
然后他跑过了转角……
- You just took it?
- I just followed him.
- 你就拿来了？
- 我只是跟着他，
- I didn't... I had it in my hand.
- Why was he running?
- 我没有…我就拿在手里了。
- 他为什么要跑？
- Hugh, what happened?
- I'm fine, I'm fine.
- 休，出什么事了？
- 我没事，我没事。
- Did you put this down?
- Amir, why the fuck did you take that?
- 这是你放下的吗？
- 阿米尔，你他妈的为什么要拿这个？
- I thought I saw you put it down.
- I did not touch that thing.
- 我以为我看到是你放下的。
- 我没碰过那玩意儿。
I don't know what that is
or why you grabbed it.
我不知道那他妈的是啥，
也不知道为什么你要拿它。
- Guys, what happened?
- Okay. We were at the other house.
- 两位，发生什么事了？
- 好吧，我们到了那所房子，
Hugh went around the side.
I thought I heard a noise.
休从旁边绕过去，
我想我听到了一阵动静。
You made some kind of sound,
and then you saw what?
你好像弄出了什么声音，
然后你看到什么了？
Something.
You won't tell me what you saw.
一定有什么，
你不想告诉我你看到了什么。
I don't understand what's going on.
What did you see?
我不明白这是怎么回事。
你看到什么了？
- I don't...
- What did you see?
- 我不想……
- 你看到什么了？
That has nothing to do with anything...
那和我们应该关心的事情…
that we should be fucking concerned with.
…屁个关系都没有。
What did you see?
你看到什么了？
- It's not a big deal. I'll walk it back.
- Okay, fine.
- 没什么大不了的，我送回去好了。
- 好吧，很好。
Wait. Let me open it first.
等一下，让我先打开看看。
No, Mike. What are you doing?
不，迈克，你想干嘛？
- What is it?
- I don't know. I don't know.
- 这是什么啊？
- 我不知道，我不知道。
You don't want to talk about it
and you don't want to open...
你既不想谈谈，
又不想打开盒子……
Fine! Open the fucking box!
Open the box. What do I care?
好啊！打开那该死的盒子！
打开那盒子，我在乎什么？
What is wrong? Calm down.
出什么事了？镇静。
What happened?
发生什么事了？
Holy shit, it worked.
我靠，真能开开。
I got it.
我打开了。
Open it away from your face.
别对着你脸打开。
- It's not a bomb.
- How do you know what the heck it is?
- 它不是炸弹。
- 你怎么知道它他妈的是什么？
- Don't freak out.
- Be careful.
- 别害怕。
- 小心点。
Oh, my God, It's a ping-pong paddle.
It's a ping-pong paddle.
噢，我的天哪，是一块乒乓拍，
里面有一块乒乓拍。
- Well, what's that?
- What is going on?
- 还有，那是什么？
- 这怎么回事啊？
- Oh, my God.
- What is it?
- 噢，我的天哪。
- 是什么？
These are pictures of all of us.
这些是我们所有人的照片。
These are...
这些是……
- Somebody's marked us.
- I want to try to figure this out.
- 有人给我们作了记号。
- 我想搞清楚这怎么回事。
- This is insane.
- And there are numbers on the back.
- 这太疯狂了。
- 背后都有数字。
- Hugh.
- Baby, what did you see?
- 休。
- 宝贝，你看见什么了？
- Hugh what did you see?
- What did you see?
- 休，你看见什么了？
- 你看见什么了？
Jesus Christ, man.
我说，哥们，
You can't stand there and not say anything!
What did you see?
你不能站在那里一言不发啊！
你究竟看见什么了？
Hugh!
休！
There are pictures of us in this box!
这盒子里全是我们的照片啊！
Hugh!
休！
I went to the window,
and I looked in the window.
我走近窗口，往窗口里望去。
And I saw a table...
我看见一张桌子…
with wine glasses and candles...
上面有酒杯和蜡烛…
and dinner set for eight people.
还有八个人用的晚餐。
I saw...
我看见……
Oh, my God.
噢，我的天哪。
Right. Okay, fuck you, Hugh.
是啊。好吧，去你的，休。
- I saw...
- Bullshit.
- 我看见了……
- 扯淡。
- Did you guys come and fuck with this door?
- Fuck you, Kevin.
- 你们俩有没有过来对这个门搞鬼？
- 去你的，凯文。
Did you come to the side door?
你们有没有来过这个边门？
No. You went to the side
door at the other house.
不，你去的是那所房子的边门。
They wouldn't answer the door,
so I went...
他们没有应门，
所以我走到边门……
Bullshit.
扯淡。
You dipshits walked in a circle
and knocked on this door.
你们两个笨蛋绕了一圈
然后敲了这边的门。
I did not walk in a fucking circle!
I went two blocks.
我他妈的才没绕圈子呢！
我走过了两个街区。
We went up to that house.
I knocked at the door.
我们走到了那所房子，
我敲了那里的门，
Nobody answered, so I went
and banged on the side door.
没人答应，所以我又
转过去敲了他们的边门。
- Did you see yourself, Hugh?
- No, I did not see myself.
- 你看见你自己了，休？
- 不，我没看见我自己。
- No, because you weren't there.
- I did not go in a circle!
- 是啊，因为你根本没在那儿。
- 我没在这儿绕圈！
- Fuck.
- Just calm down.
- 操。
- 冷静。
I don't believe this.
我不相信。
This still doesn't explain the pictures.
这仍然解释不了这些照片。
What's on the back of them?
它们背面是什么？
Numbers.
数字。
They're all...
We've got two, one, one.
它们都……
我们有2、1、1，
That's five.
还有5。
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Where are you going?
- I'm gonna go back over there.
- 喔，喔，喔，你要去哪儿？
- 我要回那儿去。
- Whoa.
- No, no, no. Think about it.
- 喔哦。
- 不，不，不，想想看吧，
I'm gonna go back over there.
I'm gonna ask to use their phone...
我要回那儿去，
我要向他们借用电话…
and, hopefully, I can get
in touch with my brother.
并希望我能联系上我的弟弟。
And if they're not there,
I'll just leave a note. Right?
如果他们不在那儿，
我要留下一个便条。行吗？
No.
不。
No, no, no.
That makes sense. Right?
不，不，不，
这样很合理，对吗？
- You should not go back.
- It's fine. It'll be fine.
- 你不应该回去。
- 没事的，会没事的。
It'll be fucking fine.
一定他妈的没事。
What's a note going to do?
便条有什么用？
（嘿你们好！没有吓你们的意思，
我们只想……）
If these people have pictures of us,
they might be crazy.
既然这些人有我们的照片，
他们可能疯了。
Shit! There's someone out there.
见鬼！有人在外面！
There's someone out there.
有人在外面！
- What?
- Oh, my God.
- 什么？
- 噢，我的天哪。
Oh, there's a big guy at the door.
噢，有个大高个儿在门口。
- Oh, my God.
- At the door?
- 噢，我的天哪。
- 在门口？
What should we do?
我们该怎么办？
- He's walking away. He's walking away.
- Please, please.
- 他走了，他走了。
- 拜托，拜托。
- Baby, please be careful.
- Oh, my God.
- 宝贝，拜托小心点儿。
- 噢，我的天哪。
- Baby.
- Careful.
- 宝贝。
- 小心。
- Shit.
- What?
- 见鬼。
- 什么？
What is it, babe?
那是什么，宝贝？
"Hey, there. Don't mean
to freak you guys out,
“嘿你们好！
没有吓你们的意思，
but we just wanted to borrow your
phone for five minutes tops.
“我们只想借用一下
你们的电话，顶多五分钟。
Thanks."
“谢谢。”
Two kinds.
有两种。
Regular Band-Aid or cloth?
要普通的还是布的“邦迪”？
Whatever.
什么都行。
- Cloth.
- Okay. Here we go.
- 布的吧。
- 好的，来贴上。
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
抱歉，抱歉，抱歉。
These are ones. This is a two.
We are four, five, six.
这几个是1，这个是2，
还有4、5、6。
Do you have any red markers?
你有红色记号笔吗？
Okay. Why are these three ones?
好吧，为什么这三个是1？
- This is a six. Five.
- Hugh and Lee.
- 这是个6，5。
- 休和李。
Two.
2。
Four.
4。
And that's the same picture.
那是同一张照片。
Oh, my God.
噢，我的天哪。
Somebody cut that in half.
有人把它一剪两半。
Where are these from?
这些照片是哪儿来的？
Could this be like numerology?
这会不会是用数字算命？
Like if you add up all the numbers...
比如你把你名字和生日里的…
in your name and the birthday...
…数字统统加起来……
Like life path numbers
or something like that?
像是命理的数字
或诸如此类的？
If that's the case, then they're just
crazy and it doesn't matter anyway.
如果真是这样，那他们肯定疯了，
反正跟我们没关系。
So, what do all the ones have in common?
那么这些1有什么共同点呢？
- Um, we have Lee...
- Date of birth?
- 唔，李是1……
- 生日？
- Oldest to youngest?
- There's no three?
- 年龄从大到小？
- 其中没有3？
- There's no three.
- 没有3。
Is there someone... Is there
someone that would want to be...
是不是有人…
是不是有人会想…
doing this to us?
…对我们做这事？
Is there someone that
is on someone's bad side?
是不是有人是某个人的对头？
- What?
- This was taken tonight.
- 什么？
- 这是今晚拍的。
What? How do you know that?
什么？你怎么知道的？
I bought this sweater today,
so that's from tonight.
这件运动衫是我今天才买的，
所以那是今晚拍的。
Has anyone taken a picture of you tonight?
今晚有人给你拍过照片吗？
Someone took a picture of you
when you were looking at the box.
在你看这个盒子的时候
有人给你拍了一张照片。
You were looking into the lens.
你在盯着相机镜头看。
But then it was already in the box.
但之后它已经在盒子里了。
What is that?
那是什么？
I can't tell what that is.
我不知道那是什么。
There's dots on the wall
and there's a lampshade.
上面有墙上的斑点，
还有个灯罩。
None of the others are
from tonight. Right?
其他照片都不是今晚拍的，对吗？
No. This our picture.
This is from last fall.
是的。这是我们的照片，
是去年秋天照的。
- This picture of Amir was taken over here.
- How do you know that?
- 阿米尔的这张照片就是在这儿拍的。
- 你怎么知道？
- He's standing in front of this drum.
- Guys, hang on.
- 他就站在这个鼓前面。
- 各位，等一下。
I can't figure out what this is.
我想不出这是怎么回事。
It's taken from the door?
是从门那儿拍的？
So, from behind the curtain?
所以是从门帘后拍的？
It's taken from over there.
从那儿往这儿拍。
Wait. When someone knocked
on the door, were you there?
等等，刚才有人敲门时，
你在那儿吗？
You were gone.
你人不在。
But you're looking right at the camera.
但是你直接看着相机。
So, it would be from that door,
then. Right?
所以，它是从门那儿拍的，对吗？
You don't remember... I mean,
你都不记得…我是说，
this is you, man. This is you.
这是你啊，老兄，这是你自己。
Guys, this isn't going to solve anything.
伙计们，这样解决不了问题。
What're you doing?
你要干嘛？
- I need a drink.
- I need something.
- 我需要喝一杯。
- 我需要喝点什么。
The... The pictures?
照…照片？
All right. Me too.
好吧，我也要。
It looks like my handwriting, babe.
这看上去像我的笔迹，宝贝。
Look at this.
你看这个。
It looks like I wrote this.
这像是我写的。
Okay, relax.
好吧，放松。
You're starting to freak me out.
你开始吓着我了。
That's your handwriting.
那是你的手书。
What is going on?
这怎么回事？
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
我感觉我快要疯了。
I can't stop thinking
about the fact that you...
我禁不住在想
刚才你讲的那个…
brought up a story you shared with Laurie.
…和劳瑞在一起时的故事。
Of all the stories that you could've...
你有那么多故事可以讲…
All the experiences that we've shared,
那么多我们一起经历的事，
you brought up a story about her?
可你偏偏要讲她的故事？
- I am so sorry.
- In front of everyone.
- 我很抱歉。
- 当着所有人面。
It's a crazy story.
We don't have stories like that.
那是个疯狂的故事，
我们没有那样的故事。
Oh, they're not crazy enough for you.
噢，我们的故事对你来说不够疯狂。
- Baby, it's a good thing.
- Oh, God.
- 宝贝，那是好事。
- 噢，天哪。
I don't need crazy stories like that anymore.
我不再需要有那样疯狂的故事。
All right. Hey, um, fuck this.
Let's just... Let's go.
好了。嘿，呃…去他妈的。
让我们…我们走吧。
I'm gonna go over there and, theoretically,
我要到那儿去，从理论上说，
let's go see if our
theoretical selves are there.
让我们去看看是否
我们理论上的自己在那儿。
- No, no, no.
- I'm going.
- 不，不，不。
- 我要去了。
- I'm in.
- There's some weird stuff happening here.
- 我也要去。
- 这里发生了诡异的事。
I think we should...
我认为我们应该……
- I think we should evaluate...
- Please, can we...
- 我认为我们应该判断……
- 拜托，我们能不能……
- I just evaluated and I'm going.
- Can we stay here?
- 我已经判断过了所以我要去。
- 我们能不能就呆在这儿？
- If there's another me, I want to see me.
- No. No way.
- 如果存在另一个我，我想去看看我。
- 不，不可能。
- No, no.
- Let's go.
- 不，不。
- 我们走。
- Look.
- I'm over this.
- 你看。
- 我受够了。
I'm getting sick of talking about it.
我越来越讨厌只在这儿谈来谈去，
I'm getting sick of writing about it.
我越来越讨厌只在这儿写来写去。
- The same fucking paper, the pictures...
- Wait.
- 他妈的一样的便条、这些照片……
- 等一下。
There's nobody trying to hurt us.
没人想要伤害我们。
We go find out what the hell is going on.
我们去找出这究竟是怎么回事。
What about you? You were
the one who wanted to go.
你怎么说？先前是你想过去的。
That's when I thought they might have a phone.
那是因为我以为他们可能有电话。
- Four glowsticks.
- Can we please keep two guys here?
- 拿四根荧光棒。
- 能不能留下两个男人？
- Two guys staying here? Please?
- I'm staying, I'm staying.
- 两个男人留在这里？拜托？
- 我留下，我留下。
Are you going? Amir, please.
你也要去吗？阿米尔，求你了。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
So, what? We're splitting up again?
怎么？我们又要分开吗？
No. We're not splitting up.
不，我们没有分开，
- We're just gonna go in two different groups.
- Oh. Okay.
- 我们只是分成了两个组。
- 噢，好啊。
Sticks, sticks, sticks.
荧光棒，荧光棒，荧光棒。
Do we need a towel on it?
需要裹个毛巾在上面吗？
I'm coming. Wait.
我来了，等一等。
Chill for a second. I'm coming.
别那么急啊，我来了。
- Why?
- Because I want to go.
- 怎么？
- 因为我也想去。
I'm going with Kevin.
我要和凯文一起去。
- Give us 20 minutes.
- All right.
- 给我们20分钟。
- 好的。
- And then what?
- Are we taking the bat?
- 那然后呢？
- 要带上棒球棒吗？
- No. We'll be fine.
- You will be fine. It's gonna be all right.
- 不，我们会没事的。
- 你们会没事的，一切都会好的。
We'll find out what's going on.
我们去看看究竟怎么回事。
No cars. No people.
There's nothing.
没有车子，没有人。
什么都没有。
Guys, look.
各位，你们看。
That's my house.
那是我家房子。
- Mike.
- This is my house.
- 迈克。
- 这是我家房子。
Mike, this isn't right.
迈克，这不对劲。
Mike, this is not your house.
迈克，这不是你家房子。
Mike.
迈克。
- My house.
- This is not your house, Mike.
- 是我的房子。
- 这不是你的房子，迈克。
Mike. This is not your house.
迈克，这不是你家的房子。
What is he doing? Kevin.
他想干嘛？凯文。
I see... I see Lee. Guys.
我看见…我看见李了，各位。
- We have to go.
- Let's get out of here now.
- 我们得走了。
- 我们赶紧离开这里。
Mike, we need to get
the hell out of here.
迈克，我们得赶紧
他妈的离开这里。
Someone's coming.
有人过来了。
Someone's coming. Go. Just go.
有人来了。走，快走。
That's just nuts.
这太荒唐了。
So, you saw four figures,
same as you?
这么说你们看见了四个人，
和你们一样？
Except they had red glowsticks.
除了他们拿的是红荧光棒。
Who had red glowsticks?
谁拿着红荧光棒？
They had the red glowsticks.
他们拿着红荧光棒。
We had the blue glowsticks.
That was the only difference.
我们拿着蓝荧光棒。
这是唯一的区别。
So, they must've opened the red
box when the lights went out.
所以在停电的时候，
他们一定打开了红色的箱子。
- And you didn't say anything to them?
- Would you?
- 你们没跟他们说任何话吗？
- 要是你你会吗？
No, I wouldn't.
不，我不会。
I think I would've thought I was
going to die, or something.
我觉得我一定会以为
自己要死过去了。
Okay, okay. So, that's it?
行了，行了。所以，就这些了？
Well, that and there's
this weird zone...
唔，除了这些还有一处
很诡异的地带……
that's even darker than the rest of it all.
那儿比别的任何地方都黑。
We went through that.
我们经过过那里。
We went through that
when we went down there.
我们去那儿的时候
也经过过那里。
We need to find out what's going on.
我们需要搞清这是怎么回事。
- The Internet's down. We don't have...
- We can't just sit here.
- 因特网上不了，我们没有……
- 我们不能只是干坐着。
What else?
Do you guys have any...
还有别的什么吗？
你们有没有任何……
Do you have books?
你有书吗？
Books on what? Books on comets?
什么样的书？讲彗星的书？
Comets, gravity, black holes...
什么都行，彗星、引力、黑洞……
Yeah, I've got Shakespeare, some
Henry Miller and some screenplays.
是啊，我有莎士比亚、
几本亨利・米勒和一些剧本。
Dude, I'm a fucking actor.
老哥，我他妈的是演员。
Anything about quantum physics?
有量子物理的吗？
Yeah, that's right up my alley.
是啊，那是我的拿手好戏。
Some actors read.
有的演员什么都读。
Your brother left a book at our house and...
你弟弟把一本书落在我们家了……
What?
什么？
I put it in an envelope to mail,
我把它放进信封里要寄给他，
but I-I put it in your car.
但我…我放在你车的后座上了。
- And it's about?
- I don't know what it's about.
- 关于什么的？
- 我不知道那书关于什么。
- Comets?
- It's just one of his books.
- 彗星吗？
- 那只是他的一本书。
It's always about stuff like that.
他的书都是那一类的。
Yeah, I will... I will go get
the book I don't know about.
是啊，我要…我要去取
这本我不知道的书。
- Can somebody go with him?
- Could you bring the bat?
- 有谁能陪他一起去吗？
- 你是不是带上球棒？
- Yeah.
- Yes. That's a good idea.
- 好的。
- 是啊，这是个好主意。
Please be careful, babe.
请多加小心，宝贝。
Okay.
好吧。
Should we wake up Lee?
我们该叫醒李了吗？
How could she go to sleep
in the middle of all this?
在这样的情境中
她怎么能睡得着的？
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, babe.
对不起。对不起，宝贝。
Jesus. Calm down, everybody.
天哪，镇静，各位。
Oh, baby.
噢，宝贝。
I was gonna mail it back to him.
我本打算寄还给他的。
What is it?
是什么书？
"Gravitation: An Introduction
To Current Research."
《引力：研究趋势简介》。
That's not gonna apply.
好像没什么用。
So, is his brother like
a scientist, or something?
这么说，他弟弟是科学家还是什么人？
He's just a really trippy guy.
他真的是个怪家伙。
He's really, really smart,
a real egghead.
他真的真的很聪明，
真正的学者。
But it's hard to...
It's like he thinks out loud.
但是很难……
好像他总是在那儿思考。
- He's a teacher at U.C.S.D.
- What do you got, Hugh?
- 他是加大圣迭戈分校的老师。
- 你看出什么了，休？
This is...
这是……
These are Brian's notes from
his lesson plan for his class.
这些是布赖恩讲课用的
课堂提纲笔记。
"Decoherence and Schroedinger's Cat."
He talked about this.
“退相干以及薛定谔之猫”，
他谈起过这个。
- Do you guys know what Schroedinger's cat is?
- I'm allergic.
- 你们都知道什么是薛定谔之猫吗？
- 我猫过敏。
So, it's a, um...
It's a thought experiment.
这是个，呃…
这是个思想实验。
There's a... There's a cat in a box...
有一只…有一只处在盒子里的猫，
that has, like, a 50/50 chance of living...
它有一半对一半的存活几率，
because there's a vial of poison...
因为有一小瓶毒药…
that's also in the box.
…也在这个盒子里。
So, regular physics would say
that it's one or the other.
所以常规的物理学
会告诉我们非此即彼――
That the cat is either alive or dead.
猫要么活着要么死了。
But Brian would argue
that quantum physics says...
但布赖恩会说
量子物理告诉我们…
that both realities exist simultaneously.
…这两种现实同时存在。
It's only when you open the box
that they collapse...
只有当你打开这个盒子时，
这两种现实才会坍缩到…
into a single event. Right?
…单一的事件。明白吗？
So, listen to this.
This is what he's written.
所以，听听这个，
这是他写下的：
"There is another theory:
“还存在另一种理论：
that two states continue to exist...
“两种状态继续存在，
separate and decoherent from each other,
“但彼此之间相互分离互不相干，
each creating a new branch of reality...
“基于这两种结果，每一种…
based on the two outcomes.
“…都创造出一支新的现实。
Quantum decoherence ensures
that the different outcomes...
“量子退相干保证了
这两种不同的结果…
have no interaction with each other."
“…不会再有任何的相互作用。”
- Hold on.
- Well, that explains it.
- 等一下。
- 是啊，这下可以解释了。
So we're in the box.
We're the cat.
所以我们就处在盒子里。
我们就是那猫。
We're both alive and dead.
我们既活着又死了。
So, there are... There are two
separate realities, and...
所以，存在…存在
两个分离的现实……
presumably until the comet passes.
大概直到彗星经过。
- Until the comet passes?
- Okay.
- 直到彗星经过？
- 好吧。
Or decoherence is maintained and
those two separate realities...
或者退相干一直持续着，
这两个分离的现实…
will remain separate once the comet passes.
…在彗星经过时将保持分离。
Everybody will be fine.
大家将平安无事。
Decoherence keeps us separate.
退相干使我们保持分离。
Right.
是的。
Why are the other us contacting
us then in this way?
那为什么另外的我们
要以这种方式和我们接触？
They didn't want to.
他们没想接触。
Who got the pictures?
Who... The numbers?
谁弄的这些照片？
谁…还有这些数字？
We started it when we went
to find a house with lights.
是我们开的头，因为我们
去找那所亮着灯的房子。
Yeah, maybe they didn't
mean the box for us.
是啊，也许这盒子
不是留给我们的。
The box isn't for us.
这盒子不是给我们的。
What if we've already
interacted with ourselves?
要是我们已经和我们自己
有过相互作用了会怎么样？
So, we're collapsing
on ourselves right now.
那么我们现在就会
坍缩到我们自己身上了。
Not if we stay separate
from each other.
但如果我们还是保持
彼此分离的话就不会。
It's already too late.
We've already been there.
现在已经太晚了，
我们已经去过那里。
Do you remember that movie
Sliding Doors?
你们还记得那部电影吗，《滑动门》？
【又译作《双面情人》（1998）】
Where just a fraction of a second...
里面讲在几分之一秒之内，
there could be two realities?
就可以有两个现实？
In one, she runs and tries to get
on the subway and she can't.
其中一个，她跑着想上
那班地铁，但没上去。
She gets her hand stuck in the door.
她把手卡在车门上。
In the other one, she gets
through and there's two...
在另一个中，她上了车，
所以存在两个分叉的现实……
If we're collapsing right now,
I'm gonna collapse on them.
如果我们现在就坍缩，
我希望坍缩到他们身上。
I'm not gonna wait for
them to collapse on us.
我可不愿意等他们过来
坍缩到我们身上。
Whoa, whoa, Mike.
喔哦，喔哦，迈克。
I'll go over there
and I'll just kill 'em.
我要到那边去，
我要去杀了他们。
- What?
- Half-kidding.
- 什么？
- 我没太开玩笑。
- Mike, let's just...
- I love my fucking life.
- 迈克，让我们……
- 我喜欢我他妈的生活。
Let's be smart first
before we do anything stupid,
在做出任何蠢事之前
让我们先变得聪明一点，
and let's stick with that we do know.
让我们坚持我们确切了解的事。
And what's smart? Just sitting here?
Doing nothing?
什么是聪明？就坐在这儿？
什么都不做？
What we do know is that
we took this box. Right?
我们确切了解的是
我们拿了这盒子，对吗？
So, our first act should
be to return it. Yes?
所以我们首先要做的
应该是将它归还，对吗？
Fuck that. No. We're not
returning that box.
去它的吧！不，我们
才不归还那盒子呢。
I don't trust that house.
That stays here.
我不相信那所房子，
盒子必须留下。
- Wait, wait, wait.
- What's got you so freaked out?
- 等等，等等。
- 什么让你那么害怕？
- Stupid, stupid question.
- You're right.
- 愚蠢，愚蠢的问题。
- 是啊，没错。
We're not at war with the
house down the street.
我们没和街那头的
那所房子开战。
They might literally
be the same people as us.
他们可能是和我们
完全一模一样的人。
Mike's saying come over
here and let's kill us.
迈克说要到这儿来
杀掉我们自己，去他妈的！
That's right. If you do it first,
you know who you're gonna fight?
没错，如果你先下手，
你知道你会和谁打吗？
- Mike.
- You.
- 迈克。
- 你。
You're gonna run into you.
你会撞见你自己。
Who's gonna win that?
谁会赢呢？
Who did you see in the window
when you went there?
你去那里时在窗子里看见谁了？
- Did you see yourself?
- I did not see myself.
- 你看见你自己了吗？
- 我没看见我自己。
- I told you who I saw.
- Okay, okay.
- 我告诉过你我看见谁了。
- 好吧，好吧。
But what if, in that over there,
that house, what if I'm drinking?
但要是在那边，在那所房子里
我在烂饮会怎么样？
I mean, just think about that for a sec.
我是说可以考虑这种可能性吧。
That's a fucked-up Michael.
那个迈克就是个废物。
Oh, God.
噢，天哪。
I'm not gonna wait
for a fucking drunk Mike...
我可不愿等他妈的
一个醉醺醺的迈克…
to come over here and kill me.
…过来把我杀了。
And kill you and kill you and kill you.
然后杀了你、杀了你、杀了你。
I'm not waiting for that.
我不会等到那一步。
Wait, wait, wait a minute.
等等，等等，等一下。
Who did you see when you were there?
你在那儿都看见谁了？
I saw Amir, I saw Hugh, and I saw Lee.
我看见阿米尔，我看见休，还看见李。
Okay. Lee's not here right now.
好吧，李现在不在这里。
- She's taking a nap.
- What do you mean, she's taking a nap?
- 她在小睡。
- 什么意思，她在小睡？
- So, it's different, then.
- Something's off. It's not the same.
- 所以说有不一样。
- 有对不上的，不完全一模一样。
In this reality, Lee's napping.
在这个现实，李在小睡；
Maybe in that reality, you're napping?
也许在那个现实，你在小睡？
So, that's why Mike didn't see her.
所以迈克才没看见她。
Right, and if Beth is
napping in that reality...
是的，如果在那个现实里
贝思在小睡，
they don't have the book.
那么他们就没有这本书。
- They don't.
- Right.
- 他们没有。
- 是啊。
The other house doesn't have the book.
那所房子里没有这本书。
And if they don't have the book,
如果他们没有这本书，
they're not having this
conversation right now.
那么他们也不会有
现在我们这样的对话。
So, then if we get
the book from the car...
所以如果我们从
他们的车里拿到这书，
then we can avoid all this.
那我们就可以避免所有这一切了。
Take it? Take their book?
拿书？拿他们的书？
It's a possibility.
有这种可能性。
- Hugh, give me your keys.
- No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait.
- 休，把你车钥匙给我。
- 不，不，不。等等，等等。
We're not supposed to mess with any of this.
我们不应该瞎搅合这样的事。
Why would we even risk this?
为什么我们要冒这样的风险？
- He's talking about going over and fighting them.
- But why make it worse?
- 他一直在说要过去和他们开战。
- 为什么把情况变得更糟？
Because then I don't have to
go over there and kill them.
因为这样我就不必
去到那里把他们杀了。
Just give me the keys.
快把钥匙给我。
No. I don't think that we should do anything.
不，我不认为我们应该做任何事。
And you are not taking my keys.
我不会给你我的钥匙。
Where you going, Mike?
你要去哪儿，迈克？
How do we know it's exactly us?
我们怎么知道那就是我们？
What if it's just externals? What if...
如果那是外来的呢？如果……
- The dark side of us.
- Yeah.
- 我们黑暗的一面。
- 是啊。
- It's us, you guys.
- You mean, the not friendly versions?
- 那是我们，各位。
- 你是说，我们的非友善版本？
Well, if it's us, then this
could be... Is it a good thing?
好吧，如果那是我们，
那么这可能…这是好事情吗？
It sounds like it would be a way to reach...
听上去像是有了条达到更高…
- higher consciousness, if we want to...
- Like an acceptance of ourselves?
- …意识层面的途径，如果我们想……
- 譬如接受我们自己？
Well, yeah. We always talk about meeting
ourselves and finding ourselves,
噢，是啊，我们总是谈论
面对自己和发现自己，
and here we have an opportunity...
现在我们有了一个切切实实地…
to actually physically find ourselves.
…从根本上发现自己的机会。
That's a lot of pressure.
那真是压力巨大。
- Look who's joined us.
- Hi, everybody.
- 看谁又加入我们了。
- 嗨，各位。
- How are you, honey?
- Okay.
- 你好吗，亲爱的？
- 不错。
Welcome back to your own dinner party.
欢迎回来你自己的晚餐会。
Yeah. How's my dinner party going?
是啊，我的晚餐会进行得如何？
- Super missed you.
- It's going.
- 超级想你。
- 还在进行。
I have an idea.
我有个主意。
I have an idea that will prevent them...
我有个主意可以阻止他们…
from getting the book from the car.
…从车里拿到这本书。
What are you talking about, man?
你在说什么呢，哥们？
I'm gonna go to that house, and
I'm gonna blackmail myself.
我要到那所房子去，
我要去敲诈我自己。
I'm gonna leave a note to keep Mike...
我要留下一张便条阻止那个迈克…
from having them go to the
car to get that book.
…让他们到车里
去取那本书的行为。
What do you mean, a blackmail note?
你什么意思，一张敲诈便条？
Something I know that
I don't want revealed.
某件我自己知道
但不想让人知道的事。
What are you talking about?
你在说什么呢？
The thing with Beth.
我和贝思的事。
The thing with Beth?
你和贝思的事？
I thought you and Hugh
worked that out years ago.
我还以为你和休之间
几年前就解决了呢。
This is the worst idea I've ever heard.
这是我听过的最糟糕的主意。
It's amazing,
'cause it would work on me.
那样很奇妙，
因为那会逼我就范。
- Going over there...
- It's the same person.
- 到那儿去……
- 那是同一个人。
We don't... You don't know that.
我们不知…你不能确定。
- This will pass.
- It's brilliant.
- 这一切会过去的。
- 这主意太棒了。
- No. It is not brilliant.
- It's brilliant.
- 不，这主意一点也不棒。
- 这主意很棒。
Dude, no. I know this look in your eye.
老兄，不，我知道你眼神的意思。
Mike, no.
迈克，别。
Why would he even say that?
他为什么要那么说？
Divergence. Otherwise,
it's just the same people.
分叉。不然的话，
就是完全一样的人。
What's going on?
怎么回事？
And if it's the same people,
如果那是一样的人，
then why not just leave each other alone?
那为什么不彼此井水不犯河水呢？
That's what I would want me to do.
那也正是我要求我自己做到的。
That might be the best thing to do.
那也许是最该做的事。
- Right?
- You doing okay?
- 对吗？
- 你还好吗？
Yeah, yeah.
还好，还好。
I don't know if I'm woozy from
the drops or if it's like...
我不知道是因为药滴
导致我晕乎乎的还是因为……
- What drops?
- 什么药滴？
- Um...
- Did you give her...
- 唔……
- 是你给她的……？
Yeah, well.
She wanted to take...
是的，可…
她想要尝…是我。
I just felt so weird before.
之前我只是感到太怪异了。
- It's this stuff I brought, this rescue remedy.
- What is it?
- 就是我带来的这东西，拯救治剂。
- 那是什么？
It's got echinacea, golden seal,
passion flower and a little ketamine.
就是些松果菊、金印草、
西番莲和一点开他敏。
I swear to God.
我向老天发誓。
- Ketamine?
- A little ketamine?
- 开他敏？
- 一点开他敏？
- It's not like you're going to go into this...
- Beth.
- 那东西不太可能把你变得……
- 贝思。
- What?
- I'm so sorry if I'm wrong here...
- 什么？
- 如果我说错了或者我说了…
and I'm saying something
incredibly inappropriate.
…什么特别不恰当的话，
那么我很抱歉。
What?
你要说什么？
Did you put any of that in the food?
你有没有把那东西放在食物里？
- Yes. That would explain a lot.
- Lee asked me for some.
- 是啊，这样好多事就解释通了。
- 李问我要了点。
Oh, come on, Amir.
噢，拜托，阿米尔。
Are you serious?
你当真这样想？
I had to ask.
我必须问一下。
She asked to take some
and I gave her some.
她问我要了点，
所以我给她了点。
When we did the mushrooms years ago,
几年前我们吃迷幻蘑菇，
we talked about it, and I put
them in the spaghetti sauce.
是事先说好后，我才把它们
放到意大利面酱里的。
That was a group decision.
那是集体的决定。
I know we agreed,
but I had to ask because...
我知道我们都同意了，
但是我不得不问，因为……
You think that I would just
put drugs in your food?
你认为我会直接把药
放到你们食物里？
Oh, my God.
噢，我的天哪！
Okay. I'll show you.
好吧，我给你看。
On top of all this,
you think I'd drug you?
别的先不说，
你认为我会给你们下毒？
- I'll show you.
- Let's just see how much is in there.
- 我拿给你们看。
- 让我们看看还剩多少。
This is the vial I brought.
这就是我带来的小瓶。
Yeah, and a quarter of it is gone.
是啊，少了四分之一。
But that's... She's had
a couple of drops out of it.
但那…她从瓶里取了好几滴。
- That's it.
- This is, like, high-grade pharmaceutical...
- 就这样。
- 这应该是高级别的配方药吧…
- It is watered down.
- You can't.
- 兑过水的。
- 你不能。
You opened it up and watered it down?
你打开瓶子兑的水？
Okay, but if you took enough of it,
好吧，但如果你用得足够多，
isn't it true that you
would have hallucinations?
还是会产生幻觉，
这是事实吧？
You would have to have a massive dose.
那你得用很大剂量才行，
You would have to take the entire bottle.
你得把整个那一瓶服了。
Okay. Fine. But is it true?
好吧，行。但这是事实？
- Yes.
- Okay. And is it also true...
- 是的……
- 好的。另外它还会…
that one of the other
effects can be paranoia?
…使人疑神疑鬼，
这也是事实之一？
Yes, but you...
是的，但是你…
- Again, you would have to have all of it.
- The whole bottle.
- 再说一遍，你得全部用掉。
- 整个一瓶。
- The whole bottle.
- And it would never...
- 整个一瓶。
- 那绝不可能……
Even if all of us took a bottle each,
即使我们每个人都各喝掉一瓶，
it would never create a mass hallucination.
也绝不可能产生集体幻觉。
- I'm not a criminal.
- It would be a nice conclusion right now.
- 我不是罪犯！
- 那样的结论比较容易接受。
Wouldn't this be great
if we were hallucinating?
说我们产生了幻觉，
这样不是很安心吗？
- Well, it's not the explanation.
- Fine.
- 但不是这样解释的。
- 好吧。
- I believe you.  - I asked for it.
- This is the bottle.
- 我相信你。　- 是我要喝的。
- 就是这瓶子。
- She asked for it. I gave her some.
- Okay.
- 她问我要，我给了她一点。
- 好吧。
I-I did not drug your food.
我…我没有给你们的食物下毒。
- I did not drug your food.
- I...
- 我没有给你的食物下毒！
- 我……
- Get it?
- Lay off, okay?
- 懂了吗？
- 别激动，好吗？
I swear to God.
天哪。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Hey, where'd you get this?
This is so cute.
嘿，这你从哪儿弄来的？
太可爱了。
Oh, I got it at, Galaxy.
That thrift store.
噢，我是在“星系”买的，
就是那家廉价商店。
Oh, I love that place.
噢，我喜欢那地方。
- That's great.
- They have such cute stuff.
- 太棒了。
- 他们有这样可爱的东西。
I just... I need a drink.
我想…我需要喝一杯。
Yeah.
是啊。
Okay.
好。
I just want to wake up
and start again, you know?
要是能醒过来重新
来一遍就好了，你知道？
Blue.
蓝色。
It's not even cracked.
红的都没打开过。
What are we gonna do?
我们怎么做？
We have to get the fuck out of here.
我们得赶紧离开这里。
Okay.
好的。
- Okay. Let's take...
- Take the book.
- 好的，我们拿上……
- 拿上这本书。
- Take the book.
- Do we take the box?
- 拿上这本书。
- 要拿上这盒子吗？
- Take the box. This is what they...
- Take it.
- 拿上这盒子，这是他们……
- 拿着。
Hey. You okay?
嘿，你好吗？
Where'd you go?
你去哪儿了？
I need a drink.
我需要喝一杯。
Hey. What... Where'd you go?
嘿，那什么…你去哪儿了？
I went to the house, dude.
我去那所房子了，哥们。
- I told you.
- What happened?
- 我告诉过你。
- 发生什么事了？
I just dropped the letter off.
我只是投了一封信。
I saw the book.
我看到那书了。
I was gonna... I was gonna
smash the window...
我本来想…我本来想砸破车窗…
and take the book.
…把书拿到。
I didn't do that, though.
I did not do that.
但是我没那么做。
我没那么做。
I just dropped off the letter, and, um...
我只是把信送到，然后，呃…
then I was gonna wait,
to see their reaction.
然后我就等着，
想看看他们的反应。
But I fuckin' freaked out.
但是我越来越害怕，就回来了。
- You've been gone, like, five minutes.
- Like 45 minutes, dude.
- 你好像只去了五分钟时间？
- 有大概45分钟，老兄。
- No. No.
- Bullshit.
- 不，不。
- 胡说。
You talked to me.
You went in the kitchen.
你和我说完话，
你走进了厨房。
You've been gone for five,
maybe 10 tops.
你去了5五分钟，
也许顶多10分钟。
You're fuckin' crazy.
你他妈的疯了。
Oh, Mike. Mike, don't do that.
噢，迈克。迈克，别那么做。
- Oh, my God.
- Mike, what was...
- 噢，我的天哪。
- 迈克，怎么……
Don't do this.
别那么做。
Mike, please? Why now?
迈克，求你了？为什么现在？
Why not now, honey?
Why not now?
为什么现在不喝，亲爱的？
为什么现在不喝？
- Where are Hugh and...
- We were in the kitchen.
- 休人呢……？
- 我们去了厨房。
Where's...
人呢？
- Where's Hugh?
- Where's Amir?
- 休人呢？
- 阿米尔人呢？
More importantly, where's the box?
更重要的是，那盒子呢？
Oh, my God. They took the box.
噢，我的天哪，他们取走了盒子。
Mike, where did they go?
迈克，他们去哪儿了？
- I have no clue where they went.
- You gotta be kidding.
- 我不知道他们去哪儿了。
- 你没开玩笑吧。
You were in here. What happened?
你就在这里，出什么事了？
我们都在厨房。
Where's the book? Where's the book?
书在哪儿？书在哪儿？
Why would they bring that
to the other house?
为什么他们要拿到
另一所房子里去？
They said they wanted to take it back
so they could make everything right.
他们说他们想把盒子拿回去，
这样一切都会重回正轨。
They wanted to return it, so everything
would be fine from the beginning, but...
他们想取回去，这样一切
从一开始就正常了，但是……
- Why would they bring the book?
- It's the one thing that we wouldn't...
- 那他们为什么要拿走那本书？
- 这件东西我们不愿……
- They took everything we have.
- Wait a minute.
- 他们拿走了我们所有东西。
- 等一下。
We have to go get them.
我们必须去找他们。
Wait a minute. They were the
first ones to leave, right?
等一下。他们两个是
第一个离开的，对吗？
And then they... They came back.
They said they saw something.
然后他们…他们回来了，
他们说他们看见了什么。
They've been acting weird ever since.
自始至终他们都表现得怪怪的。
- What are you implying?
- Oh, my God.
- 你想说什么？
- 噢，我的天哪。
- No, that's... Well, you guys left, too.
- Think about it.
- 不，那…可你们几个也离开过。
- 好好想想吧。
I mean, everyone... You left, too.
我是说，人人都…你也离开过！
- Amir came back and got so quiet,
- Come on.
- 阿米尔回来后变得很沉默，
- 拜托！
And then... and he didn't...
然后…然后他没……
- Amir was being totally weird.
- I'll bring 'em back.
- 阿米尔是一直相当古怪。
- 我去带他们回来。
- I'll see what's going on.
- Baby, you're not...
- 我要去看看是怎么回事。
- 宝贝，你不能…
- You're not going anywhere.
- I'll be back.
- 你哪儿也不能去。
- 我会回来的，马上回来。
I'm just gonna go bring them back...
我只是去带他们回来…
and find out what the hell's going on.
顺便搞清这他妈的怎么回事。
- No. You're not leaving.
- Baby, relax. What?
- 不，你不能离开！
- 宝贝，放松点。怎么？
- No.
- It's fine. I'll be back.
- 不行！
- 没事的，我会回来的。
I'm not gonna let you go.
我不会放你走！
It would be fucking crazy.
这太他妈的扯了！
Okay. So, what are we gonna do?
好吧，那我们该怎么办？
I mean, they're out there, and I swear
to God, I'm gonna have a heart attack.
我是说，他们俩还在外面，
天哪，我都要发心脏病了。
- We've gotta do something.
- Let's have a drink.
- 我们得做点什么吧。
- 我们来喝一杯吧。
We don't even know if that was them.
我们甚至不知道那就是他们。
Would you quit saying that, please?
能不能求你别怎么说了？
No, but if it wasn't them,
then Mike is right,
可如果那不是他们，
那迈克是对的，
and we can't trust the other house.
我们不能相信另外那所房子。
- We can't trust ourselves.
- That's right.
- 我们不能相信我们自己。
- 没错。
- Jesus.
- And our clues just left the house.
- 天哪。
- 我们的线索已经不在这房子里了。
No. Wait.
不，等等。
The clues are still here.
线索仍在这房子里。
If they had the pictures, then...
如果他们有了那些照片，那么……
Mike, you took that picture
of me and Kevin. Right?
迈克，我和凯文的那张合影
是你给我们照的，对吗？
Do you have it here?
你这儿有吗？
I-I can't take this anymore.
I can't take it.
我…我受不了这个。
我再也受不了了。
- Sweetheart...
- Can you at least go look for it?
- 亲爱的……
- 你能不能去帮我找找看？
I'm gonna look for another bottle of wine.
我要去找找另一瓶酒看。
This is so stupid.
这太可笑了。
Should I be keeping an eye on him?
我要不要注意着点儿他？
I feel like I don't want to hover, and...
我觉得我不想犹犹疑疑，可……
I don't know.
我不知道。
Just give it a minute, and then...
先考虑一下，然后…
go in and talk to him, I guess.
进去和他谈谈，我想。
I don't know who Mike is anymore.
Not when he drinks.
我不再认识迈克，
在他喝醉的时候。
Everything that's gone wrong with us
started when he started drinking.
他开始酗酒之后，
我们的一切都出了差错。
It's why we had to leave L.A.
这就是我们不得不
离开洛杉矶的原因，
It's why he doesn't have a career.
这也是他事业不顺的原因。
He's just... I don't know.
他变得…我不知道，
Not the man I married.
不再是我嫁他时的那个男人。
Hey.
嘿。
- Hey.
- How you doing?
- 嘿。
- 你怎么样？
How you holding up?
都还好吧？
All things considered, all right.
方方面面，一切都好。
I totally don't believe you.
我一点也不相信你。
- Yeah. Well, am I being some...
- What's going on?
- 是啊，唔，我是不是现在……
- 出什么事了？
I... Amir told me you were
gonna go to Vietnam...
我…阿米尔跟我说
你要去越南，
and Em's not going with you?
而艾米不想和你一起去？
Yeah. I...
是啊。我…
I gotta go for work for, I don't know...
我要去那儿工作，我不知道…
It's four months, I think, and,
是四个月，我想，
yeah, I want her to come along, but...
是的，我希望她也一起去，但……
She'd be crazy not to go with you.
她一定是疯了不和你一起去。
Yeah. That's what I think.
是啊，我也是这样想的。
Yeah. I don't... I don't know.
是啊。我不知…我不知道。
I mean, it's... I-I really
don't want to interfere.
我是说，这……我…我真的
不是想多管闲事，
It doesn't seem like any of my business,
这事看起来与我一点关系没有，
but I think you've always been someone...
但是我觉得你一直是那种…
who's extremely passionate about
your life and what you're doing,
…对你的生活和你所
从事的事业极端热情的人，
and if you have a partner that
seems to hesitate all the time,
如果你有一个伴侣，
她似乎总是犹犹豫豫的，
with things of life, I don't know
if that's gonna make you happy.
对生活的方方面面，
我不知道那是否能让你幸福。
Oh. She's...
噢，她……
I mean, I love her, and...
It's just who she is.
我是说，我爱她……
她就是这样的人。
- Sometimes she's a little...
- Tall?
- 有时她有点儿……
- 高？
- Crazy.
- She's a little bit tall.
- 瞎说。
- 她个儿有点儿高。
I mean, do you have to stand
on your tiptoes to kiss her?
我是说，你是不是得
踮起脚尖才能吻到她？
I...
我……
Sometimes people just fit well.
有的时候人和人就是不匹配。
- Laurie...
- Like that Sharks game?
- 劳瑞……
- 喜欢那个“鲨鱼”游戏吗？
Come on, you can't tell me
we don't fit well.
拜托，别跟我说我们不匹配。
I had to do yoga for a week
afterwards to recover.
那之后为了恢复，
我不得不去练了一周的瑜伽。
I do remember that.
这事我的确还记得。
I just think that maybe...
我在想也许……
Laurie.
劳瑞。
I'm sorry. I'm crossing all
kinds of boundaries with you.
对不起，我跨越了你所有的界线。
Yeah.
是的。
- Baby?
- Hi.
- 宝贝？
- 嗨。
You know, I think you're right...
你知道，我觉得你是对的…
that everything happens for a reason.
任何事发生都有原因。
Should I get the bat?
要我去拿棒球棒吗？
For you or for me?
给你用还是给我用？
Could be either.
都可以。
What are we doing here?
我们在这儿干嘛？
If I'm losing it over there,
I'm losing it here.
如果我在那边失去了理智，
那么在这边我也失去了。
- It doesn't have to be like that.
- Sure, it does.
- 不一定非得如此。
- 当然是的。
It's the same thing.
这是一回事。
No, it's not.
不，不是的。
How do you figure?
你怎么知道？
Because there's no way that anybody
over there, or... or anywhere,
因为不可能存在任何人，
无论在那边还是…哪边，
loves you as much as I love you right here.
比我更爱我身边的这个你。
I fucked up.
我一团糟。
- Hi.
- Hey.
- 嗨。
- 嘿。
How you doing?
你怎么样？
Fine.
呃…很好。
Is... Is everything okay?
一切都…都好吗？
Is there something going on?
有什么事让我知道吗？
Beth just walked up to me and...
贝思刚才来找我……
she didn't really say much,
but she said that she...
她当然没说太多，
但是她说她…
saw you and Laurie talk
in the hallway, and...
…看见你和劳瑞
在过道里谈话……
Jesus Christ, Em. I think we have...
天哪，艾米，我觉得…
some more important things
to worry about right now...
…相比贝思所说的事，
我们现在有…
than what Beth is saying.
…更重要的事要担心。
Jesus Christ.
老天哪！
- Are you kidding me?
- That would be the generator.
- 不会吧？
- 一定是发电机坏了。
- Hold on.
- All right. You know what to do.
- 等一下。
- 好吧，你知道怎么做。
- We have thousands of matches at home.
- Don't burn yourself.
- 我们家里有无数的火柴。
- 别烧到你自己。
- Kevin, do you have matches?
- Yeah, I got some.
- 凯文，你有火柴吗？
- 有，我这儿有几根。
Here.
给。
- Hold it.
- I don't know...
- 拿住。
- 我不知道……
- You want to put this on the table?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- 你想把这放到桌上去吗？
- 好的，好的。
- Whoa.
- That was right out front.
- 喔哦！
- 就在前面。
- Are you kidding?
- That sounds like one of our cars.
- 开玩笑？
- 听声音像是我们的车。
Like one of our cars getting broken into.
像我们的一辆车被砸窗了。
Look, I'm going out there.
I can't stand this.
听着，我要出去看看，
我不会容忍这个。
- I'm gonna go see what's going on.
- Not without the rest of us.
- 我要去看看是怎么回事。
- 你不能一个人去。
- Let's just all go.
- Fine. Then let's all go, but I'm going.
- 那我们一起去。
- 好啊，我们一起去，反正我要去。
- I'll get my coat.
- I don't think we should.
- 我去拿外套。
- 我觉得我们不该出去。
- Let's get a flashlight.
- We'll be fine.
- 我们拿上荧光棒吧。
- 我们会没事的。
- Here. I got one here.
- You guys lead, okay?
- 给，我这儿有一根。
- 你们几个带头，是吗？
- You ready?
- Okay. Here we go.
- 准备好了？
- 好了，我们走。
- Stay close. Stay close.
- Here we go.
- 靠紧一点，靠紧一点。
- 我们走。
- Where did it come from?
- I don't know.
- 那是从哪儿来的。
- 不知道。
That's it, right?
就是这车，对吗？
- Oh, my God.
- Jesus. Look.
- 噢，我的天哪！
- 天哪，快看！
- Is there anything in there?
- I don't see anything.
- 里面有什么东西吗？
- 我没看见有东西。
Oh, my God. Should we...
噢，我的天哪！我们该……
- Should we check our cars?
- That's crazy.
- 我们该检查一下我们的车？
- 太荒唐了。
Yeah, why doesn't everybody
check their own car.
是啊，每个人最好
检查一下自己的车，
- See if we find anything else.
- Let's look at our cars.
- 看看是否能发现点什么。
- 我们去看我们的车。
- Okay.
- All right. After you.
- 好吧。
- 好吧，你先请。
Is everyone nearby?
大家靠的很近吗？
We shouldn't spread out too much.
我们不应该分得太开。
- Hey.
- Everything okay?
- 嘿。
- 一切都好吗？
Yeah. I just...
是的，我想…
put this ring on that
you got me at the fair.
…把你在集市上给我买的
那枚戒指戴上。
Remember? I know it's...
记得吗？我知道它……
I know it's cheesy,
but I just wanted to have it on.
我知道它很俗气，
但我就是想戴上它。
Cheeseball.
巨土。
- It was a good day.
- 那天很开心。
- 那天是很开心。
Are we okay?
你还好吗？
- Yeah, babe.
- After that whole Laurie thing?
- 好的，宝贝。
- 在劳瑞搅合了之后？
Yeah.
呃…是啊。
I don't know what the hell she's thinking,
我不知道她究竟怎么想的，
but yeah, we're good.
但是的，我们很好。
Come here. Hey.
到这边来。嘿。
Is everything okay with Hugh's car?
休的车没大碍吧？
- What do you mean?
- Well, did they take anything?
- 你什么意思？
- 他们拿走什么东西了吗？
You just checked on his car.
Did they take anything?
你刚才看了他的车，
他们有没有拿走东西？
Doesn't make any sense at all.
完全没有道理。
Do you think it's just someone
trying to intimidate us?
你认为这只是
有人想吓唬我们吗？
Intimidate? No. I... It's...
吓唬？不。我…这……
None of this... It doesn't...
所有这些…都不……
I mean, it's like they're
looking for something, and...
我是说，看起来好像
他们在找什么东西……
- But there's nothing in there.
- Exactly. There's nothing in there. So, why...
- 但那里面什么都没有。
- 没错，什么都没有，所以为什么……
They could see that there's nothing in there.
他们可以看见里面没有东西。
- We could see that there's nothing in there.
- I know.
- 我们可以看见里面没有东西。
- 我知道。
Why break the window
if there's nothing there?
如果里面没有东西，
为什么要砸破车窗？
- That doesn't make any sense.
- None of this makes any sense.
- 那太没道理了。
- 这一切都没道理。
Where were you?
你去哪儿了？
I went and got this ring.
我去取这枚戒指。
Nice.
不错。
All right, hold on.
Let's-Let's...
好吧，等一下。
让我们…让我们……
Let's just try and figure out...
让我们试着搞清楚…
why we would break into
a car... Hugh's car...
…为什么我们要
砸破一辆车…休的车…
knowing that the book wasn't there.
明明知道书不在那里。
Well, we're assuming
that the book is the motive.
我们一直假设书是动机，
What if the motive is completely different?
但如果动机完全不同呢？
- Did you hear something?
- What the hell is that?
- 你们听到什么吗？
- 那是什么？
It's outside. No, Mike,
Mike, Mike, Mike.
在外面。不，迈克，
迈克，迈克，迈克！
- Oh, shit! There's someone coming.
- What?
- 噢，见鬼！有人过来了！
- 什么？
They're coming over here, guys.
他们到这里来了，各位。
Yeah. It's Hugh.
是啊，那是休。
- Is it Hugh?
- Is it Hugh and Amir?
- 是休吗？
- 是休和阿米尔？
Yeah, it's blue.
It's Hugh and Amir. Cool.
是的，蓝色的，
是休和阿米尔，别怕。
- They're coming to the door.
- Are you sure?
- 他们朝门走过来。
- 你确定吗？
- It looks like it.
- Oh, baby.
- 应该是的。
- 噢，宝贝。
Are you all okay?
你们都还好吗？
- Hey, where have you been? What happened?
- Okay.
- 嘿，你们去哪儿了？发生什么事了？
- 好了。
What have you been... Why did
you take... What did you do?
你们都干…为什么你拿……
你干什么去了？
- Can you please tell us what happened?
- We went to...
- 能不能告诉我们发生什么事了？
- 我们去…
We went to make a phone call,
and then when...
我们想去打个电话，然后当…
when we looked in the door, we saw...
当我们往门里看时，我们见到…
We saw this, basically.
I, I got startled.
我们见到了这些，大致一样。
我，呃…我吓了一跳，
I fell over. I hit my head.
We went back to the house to...
摔倒了，碰破了头。
我们回到这所房子……
Wait. You already came back here.
等等，你们已经回来过这里。
We already heard this story.
我们已经听过这故事。
Why are you telling us
this story again?
为什么你又给我们
讲一遍这个故事？
- You came back with the box.
- Wait. What?
- 先前你们带回了一个盒子。
- 等等，什么？
Because you came back,
and after you hit your head...
因为你们回来过，
你弄破了你的头…
We gave him a Band-Aid
and you gave us the...
我们给他贴了“邦迪”，
你给了我们那个……
But not that Band-Aid.
但不是这块“邦迪”。
- What do you mean?
- Oh, my God. I gave you a cloth Band-Aid.
- 你什么意思？
- 噢，天哪！我给你贴的是布条“邦迪”。
Wait a minute. Hugh...
There was a Hugh and an Amir here?
等一下，休……
这里有过一个休和一个阿米尔？
Yes. And you left with the book.
是的，而且你们把书带走了，
You left with the pictures,
and we didn't know where you went.
你们还带走了照片，
我们不知道你们去哪儿了。
We were at a house where
everybody had red glowsticks.
我们去的那所房子里
人人都有红荧光棒。
- You had red glowsticks.
- Do you understand?
- 你们有红荧光棒。
- 你们懂吗？
We... We have red glow...
We took them from the other house.
我们…我们有红荧光…
我们从那所房子拿的。
- Right.
- Look. Look.
- 是的。
- 你们看，你们看。
Is that... Look. That box of
red glowsticks is unopened.
这不是…看，那盒红荧光棒
压根就没开封过。
Guys, if they started here,
they belong here.
各位，如果他们开始在这里，
那么他们就属于这里。
They're in the right house.
他们来对了房子。
- Well, welcome back.
- Welcome back.
- 是啊，欢迎回来。
- 欢迎回来。
- Jeez, man, I'm sorry.
- That's all right.
- 天哪，对不起了。
- 没关系。
Sorry.
对不起。
So, guys, what was the other Mike like?
What was he doing?
那么，另一个迈克怎么样？
他在干嘛？
The other Mike is...
He's worried about you.
另一个迈克……
他在为你烦恼。
So, it was you guys who left us the note.
那么是你们俩给我们留的条。
No, I never got out with that note.
不，我没能送出那便条。
We ended up with two notes.
我们最后有了两张便条。
And so did we.
我们也一样。
- Well, where's...
- We have two notes.
- 那哪里……
- 我们有两张便条。
One that was written here
and one that was left on the door.
一张是在这儿写的，
一张是留在门上的。
If you didn't, and if
the other Hugh didn't,
如果你们没留，如果
其他的休也没留，
then who has been leaving the notes?
那这些便条是谁留下的？
"Quantum decoherence ensures
that the different outcomes...
“量子退相干保证了
这些不同的结果…
have no interaction with one another."
“…不会再有任何的相互作用。”
So, that one note has been
written at least four times.
所以那张便条至少
已经被写过四遍了。
Well, how many Hugh and Amirs
are walking around out there?
到底有多少休和
阿米尔在那儿晃荡？
Okay, before we do anything,
好吧，在做任何事之前，
we have to figure out
how to mark our own house.
我们必须想出如何标记
我们自己房子的办法。
- Just stay inside.
- No, no. She's right.
- 就呆在房子里。
- 不，不，她说得对。
Staying inside isn't realistic.
光呆在房子里不实际。
We need some kind of marker.
We got to mark this house.
我们需要某种记号，
我们要给这房子做记号。
If every house is the same...
如果每所房子都一样…
If we put a marker
in front of the house,
那如果我们在房子前面
做上标记的话，
there could be an infinite
number of houses with that mark.
就可能会有无穷多房子
有同样的标记。
So, we have to do something random.
所以我们得做出随机的事情，
Something that can't be repeated.
Something unique.
不能被重复的事情，
独一无二的事情。
- Dice. Do we have dice?
- We have dice?
- 骰子，我们有骰子吗？
- 我们有骰子吗？
- Um, Yahtzee.
- Yeah, Yahtzee.
- 唔，“快艇”游戏。
- 是啊，“快艇”游戏里有。
If we each roll a number for each
of us, that's what? That's...
如果我们每个人都给自己
掷个数，那有多少？那有……
Six times six times six times six
times... That's hugely random.
6乘以6乘以6乘以6乘以……
那就相当随机了。
- The probability of that repeating is... tiny.
- And then what? We...
- 重复的几率就…微乎其微。
- 然后呢？我们……
But so we have to have something visual.
但我们得有看得见的东西，
I mean, should we write
it down, put it in...
我是说，我们应该写下来吗？
把它放到…
put it outside? Put it in an envelope?
放到外面？放到信封里？
- We still won't know.
- No, no, no, no.
- 我们仍然不知道。
- 不，不，不，不。
We need something to mark it.
我们需要有标记的东西。
Yeah. We put it in a box.
是的，我们把它放进盒子里。
- That's, that's...
- That's exactly what they've done.
- 那样…那样……
- 那样正是他们做的。
- They were ahead of us.
- They were making a marker for their house.
- 他们做在我们前面了。
- 他们在给他们的房子做标记。
They made a unique mark.
Only we took it.
他们做了唯一的标记，
只是被我们拿来了。
If it seems like a good idea to us,
如果这在我们看来是个好主意，
it would seem like a good idea to them.
那在他们看来也会是个好主意。
- Do you have a box?
- Yeah. Yeah, let me look.
- 你有盒子吗？
- 有，有的，我去找。
So, we need photos.
所以我们还需要照片。
- This is so crazy.
- It's par for the night.
- 这太荒唐了。
- 正好配上这一夜。
- There are a lot of pictures here.
- You can't use that picture.
- 这里有很多照片。
- 你不能用那张照片，
That's ridiculous.
那太可笑了。
- I'm the attorney for Grizzly Adams.
- Yeah, I know. This is...
- 我是“灰熊”亚当斯的律师。
- 是啊，我知道。这是……
【美国十九世纪的一位著名驯兽师】
I'm never hiring you.
我绝不会雇你。
How does this work as a box?
这个盒子行吗？
I didn't even know we had it.
我都不知道我们家有这个盒子，
It was just under
a pile of crap in the back.
它就在后面的一堆
乱七八糟的东西下面。
- If you can...
- That'll work.
- 要是你们想……
- 可以用。
So, tha... Tha...
That's your box?
所以那…那…
那是你们的盒子？
- It was here all the time.
- Of course it was.
- 它一直在这儿。
- 当然是我们的。
I'm not too happy about cutting these pictures.
我不太愿意把这些照片剪开，
And we only have pictures of
you and I together, babe.
我们只有几张你我
在一起的合影，宝贝。
I actually... I actually
have a photo of Kevin.
我实际上…我实际上
有一张凯文的照片。
- I know that's strange. Um...
- What?
- 我知道那有点奇怪。呃……
- 什么？
No, I have my, um...
不，我把我的，呃…
My checking account number is written on
the back of this old photo that I have,
我的支票帐户的账号写在了
他的这张旧照的背面，
and it's just been in my wallet forever.
所以它就一直留在了我的皮夹里。
It's right here.
就是这张。
- What?
- You know what? I-I'll just...
- 什么？
- 你猜怎么着？我…我就要…
- I'll cut this picture that we have here.
- Just use this one. It's okay.
- 我就要把我们的这张照片剪开。
- 就用这张呗，没问题的。
- Just scratch off the number.
- Cut.
- 只要把数字涂掉就行了。
- 剪好了。
Great. I think we got one
of everybody except me, so...
太好了。我想除了我
大家都有照片了，所以……
I'm glad you guys all keep a lot
of pictures of your friend, Amir.
我很高兴你们都保留了不少
你们的朋友阿米尔的照片。
Well, we'll take one of you.
行了，我们来给你拍一张。
Smile, dickhead.
笑一个，傻蛋。
Let me see.
给我看看。
It's not exactly the same.
不完全一样。
It's not the same as
the one from the other box.
这张和另一个盒子里的那张不一样。
They took a picture of me in the other
house, but it's not exactly the same.
他们在另一所房子里给我
拍了一张，但不完全一样。
This is what we're talking about.
That's a moment where it can be...
这就是我们说起过的，
那一刻可以有…
a different... a divergent moment.
…不同的……一个分叉的时刻。
That's what we're gonna do
right now with these dice.
这就是我们现在
要做的事，用这些骰子。
Wait. Since we're the blue house,
等一下，既然我们是蓝色房子，
shouldn't we use a blue pen?
我们是否该用蓝色的笔？
- Just to make it even more...
- That makes sense.
- 可以让这更加……
- 有道理。
- Yeah?
- The odds go up by three.
- 对吗？
- 几率又可提升3倍。
So, does everyone have a die?
那么每个人都有骰子了？
- What's yours?
- Beth?
- 你的数字？
- 贝思？
All right.
好的。
Six.
6.
- Hugh?
- Three.
- 休？
- 3。
- Mike?
- Four.
- 迈克？
- 4。
Six.
6。
Two.
2。
You guys know what a quick code is?
You know when you are going online,
你们知道什么是“快码”吗？
就是当你上网，
going into your bank account,
进入你的银行账户，
and when you go to your password,
当你输入你的密码时，
it'll give you a picture to choose?
它会给你一个图片让你选？
That's your quick code. That's called an
MFA. It's a multi-factor authenticator.
那就是你的快码，被称为“多因认”，
就是指“多重因素认证”。
We do 'em. We put 'em in
whenever we build our big sites.
我们做这个。只要我们建大网址，
我们就把它们放进去。
It's an icon, right?
它是一个图符，对吗？
- Sort of a random...
- A random object.
- 有几分随机性……
- 一个随机物件。
Yeah. So, what if each of these...
是的。所以如果每个盒子里…
has a random object in it to sort
of serve as that quick code, right?
…都放有一件随机的物品，
其作用就有点像那快码，对吗？
Right. Right. So, we pick
something to put in there.
是的，是的。所以我们
挑一件东西放到里面。
You could put anything in there, right?
A candle or a book or, um...
你可以放任何东西在里面，对吗？
一根蜡烛或一本书或，唔……
- The oven mitt.
- Or a ping-pong paddle.
- 烤箱手套。
- 或乒乓球拍。
Or a ping-pong paddle. Exactly. Yeah.
或乒乓球拍。对的，是啊。
Exactly.
对的？
- Well, how's this? And this is random, right?
- A coaster?
- 唔，这个怎么样？这很随机，对吗？
- 一个杯垫？
Is anything really random tonight?
今晚有真正随机的东西吗？
If you have to leave,
如果你必须离开这房子，
when you check the box,
open it up,
当你要检查这盒子时，
就把它打开，
you see that, you know
you're off to a good start.
你看到这东西，
就知道没走错地方。
I feel better.
我感觉好点了。
Okay. So we've got the box.
好了，我们有了这个盒子。
Yeah, and it only took all
night to figure it out.
是啊，花了一整夜
才想出了这一招。
We've marked the house.
If we stay together,
我们标记了这房子，
如果我们一直在一起，
keep our heads up, and nobody
wanders off, we can get through this.
保持警惕，也没人出去乱跑，
那么我们就可以顺利熬过去。
- Thanks, coach.
- Yeah.
- 谢谢，教头。
- 是的。
- You want something?
- Yeah, water. Water would be great.
- 你要喝点什么吗？
- 好的，水，水就很好。
I'm gonna get a drink.
我也要喝一杯。
I wonder how different those
numbers are from the first box?
我想知道那些数字与
第一个盒子里的有什么不同？
Let me check.
我来对一下。
Where's my calculator?
我的计算器在哪儿？
Let's see. So, if there's eight of us...
你们看啊，如果我们有8个人，
（绿色：凯文/2、迈克/2、艾米/3、贝思/3
阿米尔/4、李/5、休/5、劳瑞/5）
Let's see. So, if there's eight of us...
你们看啊，如果我们有8个人，
（绿色：凯文/2、迈克/2、艾米/3、贝思/3
阿米尔/4、李/5、休/5、劳瑞/5）
and it's six times six...
那就是6乘以6…
times six.
…乘以6。
Three different colored
glowsticks times three...
3种不同色彩的荧光棒
要再乘以3…
is 5,038,848 possible variables.
得到5038848个可能的变数。
【5038848=3*6^8】
So, that's the variable.
所以这就是可变因素。
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
（红色：迈克/1、李/1、休/1、劳瑞/2
贝思/4、艾米/4、阿米尔/5、凯文/6）
Everything okay with the numbers?
数字没问题吧？
Yeah.
是啊。
D-Do you remember what number was
written on the back of your picture?
你还记不记得你照片背面
写的是什么数字？
- Five.
- Yeah?
- 5。
- 是吗？
I found a good spot out front, just as long
as another Hugh and Amir don't come by.
我发现个前排好位置，只要另外的
休和阿米尔别过来串门。
Kevin, do you remember what number was
written on the back of your picture?
凯文，你还记不记得
你照片背面写的是什么数字？
- Six.
- Yeah?
- 呃…6。
- 是吗？
- Beth?
- Three.
- 贝思？
- 呃…3。
Hugh, do you remember?
休，你记得吗？
- I was a three.
- You sure?
- 我的是3。
- 你确定？
Yeah. What's going on in the kitchen?
确定。厨房里在弄什么？
- Pound cake.
- 磅蛋糕。
The girls are breaking out dessert...
姑娘们在准备甜点…
before the other house eats it.
免得另一所房子先把它吃了。
Hey, Mike, I need to show you something.
嘿，迈克，我必须给你看点东西。
The numbers that I remember...
我记得从另一所…
from the box that was brought
here from the other house...
…房子拿过来的那个
盒子里取出的数字…
are these numbers.
…是这些数字。
But these are the numbers
that I found here...
但这些是我在这里
发现的数字…
in this notepad.
…在这本记事本里。
And I just asked everyone if
they can remember their number.
我刚刚问了每个人是否
记得他们自己的数字。
Beth and Lee are from this house originally,
贝思和李原本就来自这所房子，
because they have never left.
因为她们从没离开过。
But the rest of us...
We are not from this house.
但我们其余的人…
我们不是来自这所房子。
We are visitors.
我们是来访者。
Which means that this Lee is not your wife.
这就意味着这个李不是你妻子。
Are you with me?
你明白我说的吗？
Well, there's more.
更有甚者，
Because Hugh and Amir...
因为休和阿米尔…
are from a third house.
…来自于第三所房子。
He just showed me his phone.
It's not cracked.
他刚给我看了他的手机，
手机没坏。
Remember that dark area
that we walked through?
还记不记得我们走过的
那块暗黑区域？
I have a feeling that whoever
walks through that...
我有种感觉，
无论谁经过那里…
is like they end up in the
middle of a roulette wheel,
…似乎最后都会落在
一个轮盘赌盘之中，
and they will just end up
somewhere by chance.
他们最终都会随机地
处于某个地方。
And whoever walks through there...
无论谁走过那里…
will not return to the house
that they just left.
…都不可能再回到他们
刚离开的那所房子。
And I think that we need to find our way
back to our house before the comet passes...
我认为我们需要找出办法回到
彗星经过之前的我们的房子，
because we... once it...
once it passes,
因为我们……一旦…
一旦它经过了，
we might just be stuck exact... here.
我们就可能被彻底困在了…这里，
Wherever we are.
不管我们在哪儿。
I don't want to be stuck here.
我不想被困在这里。
If your theory is true...
如果你的理论是真的…
If we walk through the dark space,
如果我们穿过那块暗黑空间，
and it is a roulette wheel,
而且那儿就像轮盘赌盘，
there's no way we can be sure...
那我们就不可能有可靠的办法…
that we would go back to our original house.
…让我们能够回到我们最初的房子。
I think we just stay here.
我认为我们就呆在这里。
I think we're stuck here.
我认为我们就守在这里。
I put it out near the gate.
Should be all right.
我把盒子放在外面
靠门的地方了，应该可以了。
If we all stay here,
we should be okay.
如果我们都呆在这儿，
我们应该没事的。
Don't open it.
别开。
Who is that?
那是谁？
Oh.
噢。
- What is it?
- Mike.
- 那是什么？
- 迈克。
- Oh, fuck me.
- Oh, jeez.
- 噢，妈的！
- 噢，天哪。
- "Mike, my friend,
- What is it?
- “迈克，我的朋友，
- 那是什么？
Beth plus book equals Trinidad Club.
“贝思加书等于特立尼达夜总会。
Don't let it happen,
whatever it takes, buddy."
“别让那事发生，
不惜任何代价，哥们。”
What is this?
这是什么？
It's just this note.
It's... Mike had this...
就是这张便条，
这是…迈克想到这个…
He had this crazy idea that maybe
if he left this note out there,
他想到这个疯狂的主意，
以为他把这张便条留在那里，
it could stop them getting the book.
就可能可以阻止他们拿到那书。
It's nothing.
It was a stupid idea.
没什么的，
就是个愚蠢的主意。
But our Mike didn't deliver it.
What is this?
但我们的迈克没有送过去。
这什么意思？
Just some crazy other Mike
running around. It's nothing.
另外有某个疯了的迈克
在瞎跑，没什么的。
- You know what it is? What is this?
- We talked about it.
- 你知道这是指什么？什么意思？
- 我们谈论过。
- What is it?
- Really, it's nothing.
- 这什么意思？
- 真的，没什么的，不用担心。
- Just let it go, and...
- Then why can't you tell us?
- 这件事就算过去了……
- 那为什么不能告诉我们？
Beth?
贝思？
- Mike, what is this?
- Oh, shit.
- 迈克，这什么意思？
- 噢，见鬼。
It's...
这…
Nothing.
没什么。
If it's nothing,
then why does my wife...
如果这没什么，
那为什么我老婆…
have a fucking nosebleed?
…流他妈的鼻血了？
- Oh, honey.
- Oh, God. Oh, God.
- 噢，亲爱的。
- 噢，天哪，噢，天哪。
- Beth, what the hell is this?
- I told you.
- 贝思，这他妈怎么回事？
- 我说的吧，
- I told you this was the worst.
- What is the idea?
- 我告诉过你这主意糟透了。
- 什么主意？
12 years ago. Mike and Beth.
12年前，迈克和贝思。
- You've gotta be kidding me.
- He was gonna blackmail himself...
- 你在逗我玩吧。
- 他想敲诈他自己…
- What is this?
- so they would not get the book.
- 这什么意思？
- 这样他们就拿不到书了。
This is bad. This is really bad.
这太糟了，这真的太糟了。
- Wait. You never told Hugh?
- It was on my to-do list.
- 等等，你从没告诉过休？
- 我一直想告诉的。
We have to just get
through the night, okay?
我们只要熬过今晚
就可以了，对吗？
- Let's just try.
- He told you. He said he told you about it.
- 我们加把劲。
- 他告诉过你，他说他告诉过你。
Why didn't you tell me?
为什么你不告诉我？
- Because you didn't say anything about it.
- Who else knew about this?
- 因为你又没说过什么。
- 谁还知道这事？
Who else knew about this?
谁还知道这事？！
- Lee, did you know about this?
- Yes.
- 李，你知道这事吗？
- 是的。
- Kevin, did you know?
- He told us. He told you. He...
- 凯文，你知道吗？
- 他告诉过我们，他告诉过你。他…
- Everybody knew about this.
- We thought you knew.
- 人人都知道这事。
- 我们以为你知道。
Everybody knew about this except me?
人人都知道这事就我蒙鼓里？
Hugh, listen. It's...
It's not what it seems. It's...
休，听着，这…
这不是看上去那么简单。这…
- We don't even belong here.
- You are fucking too much, man.
- 我们甚至都不属于这里。
- 你他妈的够了，老兄。
- You are fucking too much.
- Listen. We're visitors here.
- 你他妈的够了。
- 听着，我们只是这里的访客。
- This isn't our house.
- What are you talking about?
- 这不是我们的房子。
- 你在说什么啊？
This is Lee and Beth's house.
这是李和贝思的房子。
You sleep with my wife, and
this is what you're telling me?
你和我老婆睡觉，
这是你想告诉我的吗？
Check your phone.
Is your phone broken?
看一下你的手机，
你的手机破了吗？
What the fuck does that
have to do with anything?
这他妈的和这事
有屁个关系啊？
- Is your phone broken?
- What the fuck does that have to do with anything?
- 你的手机有没有破？
- 这他妈的和这事有屁个关系？！
- Just do it.
- Show us.
- 拿出来看看。
- 给我们看看。
No. My phone is not broken.
不，我的手机没破。
Now what does that have to do
with you sleeping with my wife?
现在告诉我这和你
睡我老婆有什么关系？
From the beginning of the evening,
your phone was broken.
今晚刚开始的时候，
你的手机就破了。
- No. Em's phone is broken.
- So is yours.
- 不，是艾米的手机破了。
- 你的也是。
Your... The box. The
first box that we got,
你的…那盒子，
我们拿到的第一个盒子，
we had, like, a random item.
我们有一件像是随机的物品。
W-What w-was your random item?
你…你的随机物品是什么？
What the fuck does this
have to do with anything?
这他妈的和这事
又有什么关系？
Answer him.
回答他。
- The stapler.
- No, no, no.
- 订书机。
- 不，不，不。
- What?
- We had an oven mitt.
- 什么？
- 我们有只烤箱手套。
And ours was a ping-pong paddle.
我们的是一只乒乓球拍。
- What?
- Mine was a napkin.
- 什么？
- 我的是一块餐巾。
What the fuck are you talking about?
你们在他妈的说什么呢？
Hugh, that is not my Lee. That is not
your Beth, and I am not your Mike.
休，这不是我的李，这不是
你的贝思，我也不是你的迈克。
You... You aren't mad at me.
你…你不是生我的气。
W-We're in a different...
a different reality here.
我们现在在一个不同的…
不同的现实中。
Yeah, we're in a different reality
because the reality where I am from,
是啊，我们在不同的现实中，
因为在我来的那个现实中，
my best friend didn't
sleep with my wife.
我最好的朋友
不会睡我老婆。
Hugh, do you not understand what I'm saying?
休，你没听懂我说的话吗？
This all started tonight, and if there
are a million different realities,
这都是今晚开始的，
如果存在一百万个不同的现实，
I have slept with your wife
in every one of them.
我已经在这每一个现实中
睡过你老婆了。
- You fucking...
- No, no, no.
- 你个该死的……
- 不，不，不。
Hugh! Hugh!
休！休！
Come on!
来啊！
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.  - Settle down.
- 你没事吧？
- 没事。　- 冷静，冷静。
I'm gonna get some ice.
我去取点冰块来，
我去取点冰块。
Are you okay?
你没事吧？
Sit down.
坐下。
You okay, baby?
你还好吧，宝贝？
- Here, let me give you a little of this.
- Yeah, yeah.
- 来，我来给你点儿这个。
- 好了，好了。
Okay, I'm going to put something on it.
I'll put something on it.
好吧，我要给你抹点东西，
我要给你抹点东西在上面。
You know, I've made some... some
choices, that I'm stuck with. Um...
你知道，我做出了…一些选择，
选择我留在哪里。唔……
I'm stuck here.
我留在了这里。
I'm like the dead cat, right?
我像那只死猫，对吗？
This whole night we've been worrying...
这整个一夜我们都在担心，
there's some dark version of us
out there somewhere.
担心不知在什么地方
存在着我们的暗黑版本。
What if we're the dark version?
要是我们就是暗黑版本呢？
What's that?
那是什么？
- All right.
- Goddamn it!
- 好了。
- 该死的！
Why didn't you tell me?
为什么你不告诉我？
There's someone in the house.
有人闯进了房子！
Get the hell outta here!
快滚出这里！
- Oh. No, no, no, no, no.
- Jesus. What's going on?
- 噢，不，不，不，不，不。
- 天哪，出什么事了？
- Is he all right?
- Are you okay?
- 他没事吧？
- 你还好吗？
- Who the fuck was that?
- Mike? Mike?
- 刚才他妈的是谁啊？
- 迈克？迈克？
Does anybody know what to do?
有谁知道该怎么办吗？
- Mike?
- Is he breathing?
- 迈克？
- 他还活着吗？
- Jesus Christ!
- Laurie, it's okay.
- 老天哪！
- 劳瑞，没事了。
- Calm down.
- Laurie, Laurie, stop.
- 镇静。
- 劳瑞，劳瑞，别这样。
Laurie, Jesus.
劳瑞，天哪。
- Shh.
- Kevin, shut her the fuck up.
- 嘘……
- 凯文，他妈的让她闭嘴。
It's okay, Laurie.
没事了，劳瑞。
Just breathe. You're all right.
You're all right.
深呼吸，你没事了，你没事了。
Em. Em.
艾米，艾米！
Em, where are you going?
艾米，你要去哪里？
（嘿你们好！
没有吓你们的意思……）
Just calm down. It's all right.
镇静，没事了。
- Get off me!
- Get a rag. Get a towel. Anything.
- 放开我！
- 拿块布来，拿块毛巾来，任何东西。
- Here, here, here, here.
- Get it off!
- 给，给，给，给。
- 快把它弄掉！
- Get it off! I can't fucking stand blood.
- Okay. It's off.
- 快把它弄掉！我他妈的受不了血！
- 好了，弄掉了。
It'll be all right. Just calm down.
会没事的，镇静。
Get the fuck away.
快他妈的滚！
You're scaring the shit
out of everybody.
你把我们每个人
都吓得屁滚尿流。
- Who are you?
- Who are you fucking people?
- 你是谁？
- 你们是他妈的什么人？
- And you said...
- All you guys are crazy.
- 你说……
- 你们都疯了。
You were always fucking crazy.
你们都他妈的疯了！
She's bad news.
她就是灾星。
It's been years we
haven't seen each other.
我们已经有好几年
互不相见了。
You know, Vietnamese is
a pitch-based language.
你知道，越南语是
一种基于声调的语言。
D.H.R. Yeah.
人力资源部。是的。
It really is a pitch-based language.
那真的是基于声调的语言。
- Hi.
- 嗨。
Cheers.
干杯。
And I don't think I'm working a lot.
我不觉得我工作得太多。
I have to work a lot, but
it's gonna be a nice balance.
我是有很多工作要做，
但应该保持好微妙的平衡。
What are you gonna do while he's
working? What are you gonna do?
他在工作时你怎么办呢？
你打算干什么呢？
I don't know. Just hang out.
我不知道，出去逛逛。
- Investigate?
- Yeah, investigate.
- 做调查？
- 是啊，做调查。
Fundraise. Get those Vietnamese to invest in...
筹集资金，让那些越南人投资在……
- Fundraise in San Francisco.
- Invest in the Vietnamese.
- 在旧金山筹集资金。
- 给越南人投资。
- It's supposed to be gorgeous, though.
- This time of year.
- 应该很棒的。
- 一年的这个时候。
My cousin lived over there
for about a year...
我堂兄在那儿
生活了大概一年，
and said it was just spectacular.
说那儿非常引人入胜。
- Have you been there before?
- No. Not Vietnam. Cambodia.
- 你以前去过那儿吗？
- 没去过越南，去过柬埔寨。
Cambodia was awesome.
柬埔寨棒极了。
Did you see Angkor Wat
when you were in Cambodia?
你在柬埔寨时
去看过莫高窟吧？
- Yeah.
- Good times.
- 是啊。
- 美好的时光。
Great.
太好了。
Picture this.
想象一下这个。
- Whoa. What the hell was that?
- What was that?
- 喔哦，那是什么？
- 那什么声音？
- It was like a car window, or something.
- It sounded like glass.
- 像是汽车窗子还是什么。
- 是玻璃的声音。
It sounded like a windshield.
听起来像是挡风玻璃。
That's mine. That's mine.
那是我的，那是我的。
Should we get the, the
glowsticks to take outside?
我们要不要拿上…
拿上荧光棒到外面去？
We're not going to a rave.
我们又不是去狂欢。
You want to go to a rave, party man?
你想去狂欢，派对狂人？
I don't see anybody.
我没看到有人。
You okay?
你好吗？
- Whose is that right there?
- Oh, for fuck's sake. Seriously?
- 那边那辆是谁的车？
- 噢，去他妈的，有没搞错？
- Oh, shit.
- Oh, baby.
- 噢，妈的。
- 噢，宝贝。
- I just got this. I just got this.
- I'm sorry.
- 我刚买的这车，我刚买的这车。
- 对不起。
There's no structural damage.
没有造成结构上的损伤。
- Did they take anything?
- They didn't take my fucking...
- 他们拿走什么东西了吗？
- 他们没有拿走我他妈的…
- They didn't take my stereo.
- Come on.
- 他们没有拿走我的立体声。
- 快点。
Why don't we check
the rest of our cars,
为什么我们不检查下
其余的车子，
and see what's going on.
看看有没有什么事。
- Yeah.
- Honey, where's our car?
- 是啊。
- 亲爱的，我们的车呢？
- In the driveway.
- All right.
- 在车道那儿。
- 好的。
- Em, you good?
- Yeah. I'm right up here.
- 艾米，你好吗？
- 好的，我就在这儿。
- Hey.
- 嘿。
What are you doing?
We... Guys, she's in here.
你干什么去了？
我们…各位，她回来了。
We were looking for you.
我们正到处找你呢。
- Oh, I was just, um, by my car.
- Oh.
- 噢，我就在，呃…我车那儿。
- 噢。
- You okay, babe?
- Yeah, I just... Yeah.
- 你没事吧，宝贝？
- 没事，我…没事。
- You got away from us.
- I did.
- 你躲开了我们。
- 是啊。
I guess worse things could
happen at a dinner party.
我想晚餐聚会发生
这样的事还不是最糟的。
I went and got the... the ring.
我去拿这枚…这枚戒指。
No, I could stay here.
That's a good idea.
不，我可以留在这里，
这是个好主意。
What were you doing out there?
你刚才干嘛去了？
Em. What were you doing out there?
艾米，你刚才干嘛去了？
Um, the view is really beautiful
of the comet out there.
呃，外面那颗彗星的景色
真的太漂亮了。
- Oh.
- You came in that door?
- 噢。
- 你从那道门进来的？
- Yeah.
- What's wrong with that door?
- 是啊。
- 那道门怎么了？
That's the door to nowhere.
Don't you know?
那道门不通向任何地方，
你不知道吗？
- Okay. Let's go take a look.
- Let's check it out.
- 好吧，我们去看一下。
- 我们去看看。
Everybody's sick of hearing
about the feng shui.
大家都讨厌再听到风水了吧。
- God, it's freezing outside.
- Come on.
- 天哪，外面好冷啊。
- 拜托。
You mentioned it. Let's look at it.
你先提的，我们就要看看。
How come we never use this patio?
为什么我们从不用这个天井？
Well, we never have comets.
我们从没有彗星啊。
Oh, my God.
噢，我的天哪。
W-What's it doing?
它在干嘛？
It's breaking up.
它正在解离。
- Is that what they do?
- Yeah, I guess so.
- 彗星都这样吗？
- 是的，我想是的。
So, Em, is Katherine Meriss gonna understudy
your life while you're gone for a month?
那么，艾米，在你离开的这一个月，
凯瑟琳・梅里斯会成为你的替角吗？
- Oh, no one can.
- Ooh.
- 噢，没人能替换。
- 喔呜……
- I like that.
- Oh, come on.
- 我喜欢那样。
- 噢，拜托。
I wish we could roast
marshmallows on that meteor.
我希望我们能在
那颗流星上烤棉花糖。
A long stick.
用根长棒棒。
Yeah?
谁啊？
- Em? You okay?
- Yeah?
- 艾米？你好吗？
- 怎么？
Yeah, I'm fine.
The toilet just got backed up.
是啊，我很好，
抽水马桶刚才堵住了。
You can't use that one. You
gotta use the main one, okay?
你不能用那一个，你应该
用主厕的那一个，明白吗？
Okay. I'll be right out.
好的，我马上出来。
- Oh, my God.
- Em. Em.
- 噢，我的天哪。
- 艾米，艾米。
Hey. You're up.
嘿，你起来了。
I'll make some breakfast. It'll
be ready in, like, five minutes.
我要做点早餐，
马上就好，大概五分钟。
Oh, hi. You feeling better?
噢，嗨。你感觉好点了？
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- 是的。
- 好的。
I'm gonna get dressed. I'll be back.
我要去穿衣服，马上回来。
Morning.
早上好。
You okay, babe?
你好吗，宝贝？
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
You totally passed out last night.
昨夜你整个失去了知觉。
You were mumbling.
I put you on the couch.
你一直在嘟嘟囔囔的，
我把你放到了长沙发上。
Found that in the bathroom.
在卫生间里找到的这个。
That's weird. It's you calling me.
太怪了，是你在打给我。
Hello?
喂？
# When you sing #
# 当你歌唱 #
# The stars #
# 星星 #
# Fill up my eyes #
# 充满我的双眼 #
# Galaxies pour down my cheeks #
# 星系注向我的双颊 #
# Galaxies #
# 星系 #
# Galaxies, they flood the streets #
# 星系，它们淹没街道 #
# Galaxies #
# 星系 #
# When we dance #
# 当我们起舞 #
# Eels and sea grass #
# 海鳗和海草 #
# Float on by #
# 从旁边飘过 #
# I'm 10,000 leagues #
# 我在一万里格【约5.6万公里】 #
# Beneath the sea #
# 海水之下 #
# 10,000 leagues #
# 一万里格 #
# Beneath the green #
# 绿色之下 #
[ 翻译：639 ]
[ 同步：Flake Chen ]